<Messages>
    <Message Name="brothel-one">
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=80">
            <Text>
                She went to your current brothel with a smile on her face happy that such a nice guy bought her.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She smiled as you offered her your arm, surprised to find such a kindness waiting for her.
                Hoping such kindness would continue, she went happily with you as her new owner.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=50^Disposition<80">
            <Text>
                Having heard about her new owner's reputation,
                she was guided to your current brothel without giving any trouble.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She looked up at you hopefully as you refused the use of a retainer or delivery,
                instead finding herself taken into your retinue for the day and given a chance to enjoy the fresh air
                before you bring her to her new home.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=10^Disposition<50">
            <Text>
                She was sent to your current brothel, knowing that she could have been bought by a lot worse owner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was escorted home by one of your slaves who helped her settle in.
                She seems rather hopeful of a good life in your care.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-10^Disposition<10">
            <Text>
                As your newest investment, she was sent to your current brothel.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She has been sent to your establishment under the supervision of your most trusted slaves.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-50^Disposition<-10">
            <Text>
                Not being very happy about her new owner, she was escorted to your current brothel.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She struggled as her hands were shackled in front of her. Her eyes locked on the floor,
                tears gathering in the corners of her eyes, as she was sent off to your brothel.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-80^Disposition<-50">
            <Text>
                She didn't want to provoke you in any possible way. She went quietly to your current brothel,
                without any resistance.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was dragged away to your brothel crying,
                one of your guards slapping her face as she tried to resist.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition<-80">
            <Text>
                She was dragged crying and screaming to your current brothel afraid of what you might do to her as her new owner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She looked up at you in fear as you order for her to be taken to your brothel.
                A hint of some emotion hidden in her eyes draws your attention for a moment before she unconsciously looked away,
                no doubt afraid of what you'd do to her if she met your gaze.
            </Text>
        </Group>
    </Message>

    <Message Name="brothel-many">
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=80">
            <Text>
                They went to your current brothel with smiles on their faces, happy that such a nice guy bought them.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They smiled as you offered them your arm, surprised to find such a kindness waiting for them.
                Hoping such kindness would continue, they went happily with you as their new owner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The crowds cheer and congratulate each of the girls that you buy as they walk off the stage and into your custody.
            </Text>
        </Group>

        <Group Condition="Disposition>=50^Disposition<80">
            <Text>
                Having heard about their new owner's reputation, they were guided to your current brothel without giving any trouble.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They looked up at you hopefully as you refused the use of a retainer or delivery,
                instead finding themselves taken into your retinue for the day and given a chance to enjoy the fresh air before you bring them to their new home.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=10^Disposition<50">
            <Text>
                They were sent to your current brothel, knowing that they could have been bought by a lot worse owner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They were escorted home by one of your slaves who helped them settle in.
                They seem rather hopeful of a good life in your care.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-10^Disposition<10">
            <Text>
                As your newest investments, they were sent to your current brothel.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They have been sent to your establishment under the supervision of your most trusted slaves.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-50^Disposition<-10">
            <Text>
                Not being very happy about their new owner, they were escorted to your current brothel.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They struggled as their hands were shackled in front of them.
                With their eyes locked on the floor and tears gathering in the corners of their eyes,
                they were sent off to your brothel.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition>=-80^Disposition<-50">
            <Text>
                They didn't want to provoke you in any possible way.
                They went quietly to your current brothel, without any resistance.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They were dragged away to your brothel crying, some of them getting slapped in the face when she tries to resist.
            </Text>
        </Group>
        <Group Condition="Disposition<-80">
            <Text>
                They were dragged crying and screaming to your current brothel afraid of what you might do to them as their new owner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                They looked up at you in fear as you order for them to be taken to your brothel.
                A hint of some emotion hidden in one of their eyes draws your attention for a moment before she unconsciously looked away,
                no doubt afraid of what you'd do to her if she met your gaze.
            </Text>
        </Group>
    </Message>
</Messages>
