<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="BrCk">
    <Description>
        She will cook food for the bar.
    </Description>

    <Performance Modifier="work.cooking">
        <Primary Skill="Cooking"/>
        <Secondary Stat="Confidence" />
        <Secondary Stat="Intelligence" />
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Clumsy" Threshold="30" Action="WORKBAR">
            It took her breaking hundreds of dishes, and just as many reprimands, but ${name} has finally stopped being so Clumsy.
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Entry Name="work">
            <Text>${name} is assigned to work as a cook in the kitchen, preparing food for the customers.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Retarded">
                ${name} beams like a small child when you tell her that she is cooking today. You witness as she throws
                all the nearby ingredients into the same bowl, places the bowl on the stove, and then starts punching
                the mixture as if that is an approved cooking technique. "I cook food good!" she exclaims. Whatever
                possessed you to make a retarded girl into a cook, now you know that you are committed to seeing this
                through until the end.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Assassin">
                ${name}'s skills as an assassin have left her with a slightly skewed view towards food, which she
                casually refers to as "poison masking. You are not sure whether you should have the waitresses serve
                what she cooks, and you definitely are not going to allow her to re-cook a meal that an angry customer
                sends back. Actually, there are a lot of knives in kitchens! You had not noticed that until right now.
                So many knives.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="No Arms">
                You have assigned ${name} to work as a cook in the kitchens this week. She stares at the kitchen, with
                all the pots and pans and utensils, and then back at you, and then down at her own body, as if trying to
                draw your attention to the fact that she has no hands. After silently waiting for a response that you
                never give, she turns her gaze back to the kitchen and contemplates how she will even begin with this
                impossible task.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="No Hands">
                You have assigned ${name} to work as a cook in the kitchens this week. She stares at the kitchen, with
                all the pots and pans and utensils, and then back at you, and then down at her own body, as if trying to
                draw your attention to the fact that she has no hands. After silently waiting for a response that you
                never give, she turns her gaze back to the kitchen and contemplates how she will even begin with this
                impossible task.
            </Text>
        </Entry>
        <Entry Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to cook food in the bar</Text>
        </Entry>

        <!-- In the old version, these had an influence on the job performance -->
        <Entry Name="pre-work-text">
            <Text Condition="Chef">
                ${name} understands the difference between a "Cook" and a "Chef."
                She ventures away from the recipe book occasionally, spicing each dish to her own concept of perfection.
                It is usually a great improvement.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Agile">
                ${name} looks like she is handling a dozen pots and pans at the same time without any problems!
                She is certainly efficient.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Mind Fucked">
                ${name} works efficiently, but stares off into space with that vacant mindfucked expression of hers.
                You would think there was nobody inside her brain at all, but sometimes, when she finishes cooking a dish,
                she beams a maniacal grin and starts muttering about being a "good girl." "And good girls," she
                smiles as she jams the end of the spatula into her asshole, "get dessert!"
                She giggles, removes the spatula, and then starts using it for the next dish. That cannot be hygienic.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="One Hand">
                ${name} struggles with only having one hand in the kitchen, but makes the best of it.
            </Text>
        </Entry>

        <Entry Name="work.perfect">
            <Text Condition="No Arms">
                The food is incredible! But how?! How in hell did she do it without any hands? It just.. it just boggles
                your mind. Maybe she carries the pots with her mouth? How does she plate the food? Honestly, this whole
                thing, while very impressive, has left you with far more questions than answers.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="No Hands">
                The food is incredible! But how?! How in hell did she do it without any hands? It just.. it just boggles
                your mind. Maybe she carries the pots with her mouth? How does she plate the food? Honestly, this whole
                thing, while very impressive, has left you with far more questions than answers.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Chef">
                ${name} circulates briefly among the tables, talking to the patrons and asking their preferences so she
                can customize the menu for each of them. They are amazed by her abilities, as she not only lovingly
                prepares each dish, but plates every morsel like an artist. She circulates again after they eat, asking
                how they enjoyed their courses, and taking notes to improve them the next time. Somehow, even with all
                this time out of the kitchen talking with the customers, she manages to ensure that each dish arrives
                just in time, perfectly prepared and at the ideal temperature.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Retarded">
                There is no telling how she did it, whether by blind luck or through hidden idiot savant abilities, but
                ${name} actually made good food. Great food, really. Truly surprisingly great food. She does not seem to
                understand the science of cooking, or which ingredients are which, but somehow the final product is fit
                for any master chef. "I did good cooking, yes?" she exclaims to you before grabbing a turnip and
                repeatedly bashing it against the table to "make softer." While you have never seen this particular
                method of vegetable preparation before, you cannot argue with the results. For reasons which should be
                obvious, you opt against introducing her to those customers that ask for the privilege of thanking the
                chef.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She is an absolute frenzy of culinary activity, diving from plate to plate and stove to stove with
                expert grace. The food always appears right on time, just the right temperature, and elegantly plated.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She is a master chef, and she leaves the traditional menu far behind as she prepares individualized
                tasting plates for each patron. ${name} carefully prepares an appetizer of delicate quail eggs for one
                customer while drizzling rich chocolate on a raspberry tart for another. You only receive high
                compliments from the patrons, who promise to come back for more.
            </Text>
        </Entry>
    </Messages>
</Job>
