<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="BrMd">
    <Description>
        She will staff the bar and serve drinks.
    </Description>

    <Performance Modifier="work.barmaid">
        <Factor Skill="Service" Weight="3"/>
        <Factor Stat="Intelligence" Weight="3"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Brewing" Weight="2"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Nervous" Threshold="40" Action="WORKBAR">
            ${name} seems to finally be getting over her shyness. She's not always so Nervous anymore.
        </LoseTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Charismatic" Threshold="60" Action="WORKBAR">
            Dealing with customers at the bar and talking with them about their problems has made ${name} more Charismatic.
        </GainTrait>
        <Skill Name="Service" Weight="3" />
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Brewing" Weight="1" />
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="170" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="110" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="70" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="30" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="10" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="0" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as a barmaid.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to work as a barmaid in your bar to${shift}.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="event.nympho-nowork">
            <Text>${name} let lust get the better of her and she ended up missing her ${shift} shift.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be the perfect bartender, customers go on and on about her and always come to see her when she works.
            <Text>
                ${name} was sliding drinks all over the bar without spilling a drop she put on quite a show for the patrons.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She agree to play a bar game with a client.
                Knowing every type of bar game there is, ${name} easily wins.
                The customer pays double for his drinks and leaves the bar saying that he will win next time.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} made an 11 layer drink like it was nothing. The amazed customer left her a big tip!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She pours eleven 100ml shots from a single, one litre bottle. Now there's a good barmaid!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} noticed that a client was upset about something.
                After a pleasant conversation she managed to cheer him up.
                The client left full of willpower, leaving a generous tip behind.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Bottles fly high under the ceiling when ${name} is pouring drinks for the customers.
                The amazed crowd loudly applaudes every caught bottle and leave big tips for the girl.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} mixed up what some patrons called the perfect drink.
                It got them drunk faster then anything they had before.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by the customers for her work.
            <Text>${name} had the bar filled with happy drunks.  She didn't miss a beat all shift.</Text>
            <Text>
                Today wasn't really exciting for ${name}.
                From boredom she spent some time trying to make more complicated drinks from the menu.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} propose to a client to play a drinking game with her.
                If she loses she will serve nude to the end of her shift,
                but if she wins he will be paying double. Some other patrons join the wager on the same terms.
                After a few hours the last of them drops drunk and ${name} cleaned up on money.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                When taking orders from customers, ${name} talked them into buying more expensive drinks,
                that let you make a solid profit today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is great at this job. At happy hour she was irreplaceable getting all the orders right.
                Later on she even prevented a fight between customers.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                People love seeing ${name} work and they pour into the bar during her shift.
                She mixes wonderful drinks and doesn't mess orders up so they couldn't be happier.
            </Text>
            <!-- TODO reference special-promotion as an option -->
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>${name} didn't mix up any orders and kept the patrons drunk and happy.</Text>
            <Text>${name} didn't make any mistakes today. She even earned some tips from happy customers.</Text>
            <Text>Her shift as a barmaid goes smoothly. ${name} feels more confident in her skills after today.</Text>
            <Text>${name} had some regulars come in.  She knows just how to keep them happy and spending gold.</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} spent more time talking with customers than filling their glasses.
                She didn't earn much today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                When mixing one of the more complicated cocktails,
                ${name} noticed that she made a mistake and remakes the order.
                She wasted some alcohol, but the customer has happy with his drink.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} certainly knows what she is doing behind the bar counter.
                She spends her shift without making any mistakes and earning a lot from tips.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.
            <Text>
                ${name} mixed up a few drink orders...  But they ordered the same drink so it didn't matter too much.
            </Text>
            <Text>${name} made few mistakes but none of them were lethal.</Text>
            <Text>
                Trying her best she accidentally knocks down a bottle containing one of the bars most expensive liquors.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Maybe she isn't the best and fastest, but at least every drop of a drink that she pours stays in the glass.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She agreed to play a bar game with a client.
                ${name} loses and the client spends the rest of his stay drinking on the house.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} focused all her attention on taking orders and making drinks.
                Her attitude wasn't too appealing to clients.
                Some customers left feeling mistreated and unhappy.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} wasted a few drinks by forgetting to put ice in them but it wasn't anything major.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.
            <Text>${name} mixed up people's drink orders...  When she only had four patrons drinking.</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is having a bad day and she isn't trying to hide it.
                Her bad attitude shows and rubs off on the customers, leaving a negative impression on them.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Not being very good at this, she makes few mistakes. ${name} feels that she didn't improve today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Wanting to impress a client, she throws a bottle of an expensive liquor into the air.
                Trying to catch it behind her back, ${name} fails.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                One patron, looking for encouragement or understanding from the barmaid,
                unfortunately approached ${name}. After a short conversation, he left crying.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} tried to tap a new keg of beer; consequently she spends the rest of her shift mopping the floor.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} gave someone a drink she mixed that made them sick.
                It was nothing but coke and ice so who knows how she did it.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.
            <Text>
                ${name} was giving orders to the wrong patrons and letting a lot people walk out without paying their tab.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She mixed the ordered cocktails in the wrong proportions,
                making the clients throw up from the intoxication after just one shot!
                Besides swearing at her and yelling that they will never come here again, they left without paying.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                You can see that standing behind the bar isn't her happy place.
                Being tense she made a lot of mistakes today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Not having any experience at this kind of job, ${name} tries her best.. Regrettably without results.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She gets in a drinking game with a customer.
                Being a total lightweight, she gets drunk quickly and passes out on the job.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She spends most of her shift flirting with one client and not paying much attention to the others.
                What's worse, the guy she was flirting with skips without paying the bill!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} spilled drinks all over the place and mixed the wrong stuff when trying to make drinks for people.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <!-- TODO this doesn't work yet -->
        <Message Name="special-promotion">
            Her shift was slow and hardly anyone was buying. ${name} took the initiative, announcing a special promotion.
            <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Petite Breasts|Small Boobs" Priority="0">
                Every third shot ordered by a client could be drunk from her navel.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons" Priority="0">
                Every pitcher ordered She would pour from between her breasts.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Every third shot ordered by a client could be drunk from a shot-glass between her breasts.
            </Text>
            The promotion was such a success that you almost run out of booze.
        </Message>

        <Message Name="post-work-text">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>=85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>=99" Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=50">
                ${name} looked absolutely stunning during her shift and was unable to hide it.
                Instead of her ass or tits, the patrons couldn't take their eyes off her face,
                and spent a lot more than usual on tipping her.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Charisma>=85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=35">
                ${name} surprised a couple of gentlemen discussing some complicated issue by her insightful comments
                when she was taking her order.
                They decided her words were worth a heavy tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Intelligence<30" Chance="20" Updates="Wages-=25">
                ${name} got confused when calculating the tabs,
                and seems to have damn near given away most of the alcohol.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Clumsy" Chance="15" Updates="Wages-=25">
                Her clumsy nature caused her to spill a drink on a customer resulting in them storming off without paying.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="10">
                <Text Condition="Performance<130" Updates="Tips-=10" >
                    Her pessimistic mood depressed the customers making them tip less.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>120" Updates="Tips+=10" >
                    ${name} was in a poor mood so the patrons gave her a bigger tip to try and cheer her up.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="10">
                <Text Condition="Performance<130" Updates="Tips-=10" >
                    ${name} was in a cheerful mood but the patrons thought she needed to work more on her services.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>120" Updates="Tips+=10" >
                    Her optimistic mood made patrons cheer up increasing the amount they tip.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Condition="Psychic" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=15" >
                She used her Psychic skills to know exactly what the patrons wanted to order and when to refill their
                mugs, keeping them happy and increasing tips.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="Assassin" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance>140">
                    A patron pissed her off but she just gave them a death stare and walked away.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance<150" Updates="Tips-=50;Wages-=50" >
                    A patron pissed her off and using her Assassin skills she killed him before she even realised.
                    In the chaos that followed a number of patrons fled without paying.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Horrific Scars" Chance="15">
                A patron gasped at her Horrific Scars making her sad.
                <Text Condition="Performance<160" >
                    But they didn't feel sorry for her.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>150" Updates="Tips+=25">
                     Feeling bad about it as she did a wonderful job they left a good tip.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="stat:Morality>=80" Chance="20">
                <Text Updates="Tips+=35">
                    During her shift ${name} spotted a depressed-looking lone man sinking his sorrows in alcohol.
                    She spent a short while cheering him up. Surprised with her kindness,
                    the client left her a generous tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=25">
                    One of the patrons paid way too much for his order. When ${name} quickly pointed out his mistake,
                    he said not to worry about it and told her to keep the extra as a reward for her honesty.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="stat:Morality<=-20" Chance="20">
                <Text Updates="Tips+=35">
                    During her shift, ${name} spotted a lone fellow passed out from alcohol alone at a table in a corner,
                    his wallet bulging out of his pocket. Without a second thought,
                    she discreetly snatched it out and claimed for herself.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=25">
                    One of the patrons paid way too much for his order...
                    and ${name} didn't really feel like pointing it out,
                    considering the extra money a generous tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips-=15">
                    ${name} responded to one of the vulgar remarks by a client in a much more vulgar way.
                    Needless to say, this didn't earn her any favors with the patrons that shift,
                    and her tips were a bit less than usual.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="stat:Dignity<=-20" Chance="20">
                <Text Condition="stat:Morality<=-20" Updates="Tips+=40">
                    A drunk patron suddenly walked up to ${name} and just started groping her body.
                    Instead of pushing him away immediately,
                    ${name} allowed him to take his time with her tits and butt while she helped herself to his
                    pockets and all the money inside them.
                    The rowdy client left with a dumb glee on his face,
                    probably to find out his fondling was much, much overpriced.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=15">
                    When taking an order, ${name} made sure to lean in really close for the client to get a full view of
                    her cleavage. Giving him an eyefull of tits was promptly rewarded with some extra cash in tips.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=20">
                    One of the rowdier clients gently slapped the butt of ${name} when she was passing through.
                    Her coy giggle only encouraged more clients to occasionally fondle her butt through the rest of her work,
                    which earned her some extra tips.
                </Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
