<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Wtrs">
    <Description>
        She will bring drinks and food to customers at the tables.
    </Description>

    <Performance Modifier="work.waitress">
        <Factor Skill="Service" Weight="3"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Intelligence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Agility" Weight="1"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Clumsy" Threshold="30" Action="WORKBAR">
            It took her breaking hundreds of dishes, and just as many reprimands, but ${name} has finally stopped being so Clumsy.
        </LoseTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Charming" Threshold="70" Action="WORKBAR">
            ${name} has been flirting with customers to try to get better tips. Enough practice at it has made her quite Charming.
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="170" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="110" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="70" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="30" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="10" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="0" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            ${name} has been assigned to work as a waitress at your restaurant.
            She is informed that this is a genteel and conservative establishment,
            and she should focus on providing timely and efficient service.
            <Text>
                ${name} worked as a waitress in the bar.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Mind Fucked">
                ${name} nods in understanding, but she also has a hand down her skirt,
                absent-mindedly rubbing her pussy as she listens.
                You are not entirely sure that she understands what "genteel and conservative" means here..
                ${name}'s mind fucked state may make this a more interesting shift than you anticipated.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to wait the bar to${shift}.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="event.nympho-nowork">
            <Text>${name} let lust get the better of her and she ended up missing her ${shift} shift.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="pre-work-text">
            <Text Condition="Mind Fucked" Chance="20" Updates="Performance-=5">
                ${name} unnerves the customers with her far-away stare while she takes their orders, and causes a few
                gentlemen to sweat with discomfort as she casually mentions that she is also on the menu, if they would
                like to use her for anything. They all cough, turn their heads, and try to ignore it.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air|Titanic Tits|Abnormally Large Boobs|Massive Melons" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=10">
                Customers are willing to forgive a lot of mistakes where ${name} is concerned.
                Her sexy body distracts them when they order,
                and some find themselves ordering much more expensive wine than they had
                anticipated in an effort to impress her.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Shy|Nervous" Chance="20">
                Some customers are forced to flag ${name} down to get her to come to their table,
                as her nerves and shyness get in the way of providing suitable service.
                She is not comfortable talking with all of these new people.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She's the perfect waitress. Customers go on about her and many seem to come more for her than for the drinks or entertainment.
            <Text>${name} danced around the bar dropping orders off as if she didn't even have to think about it.</Text>
            <Text>
                Knowing how to speak with customers,
                ${name} always gets the clients to order something extra or more pricey then they wanted at the beginning,
                making you a tidy profit.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Being a very popular waitress made ${name} some fans, that come here only to be served by her.
                On the other hand they leave generous tips behind.
            </Text>
            <Text>Her shift past smoothly, earning her some really juicy tips.</Text>
            <Text>
                Memorizing the whole menu and prices, taking out three or four trays at once,
                not making a single mistake for days. ${name} sure doesn't seem human.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Today she saved your place from a major disturbance. When greeting clients,
                ${name} noticed that the newly arrived group was part of a gang that was at war with another group of
                men which were already inside your place.
                She politely apologized and explained that your place was full and couldn't take such a large group.
                The men left unhappy but without giving her any trouble.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                People came in from everywhere to see ${name} work.
                She bounces all around the bar laughing and keeping the patrons happy without messing anything up.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by the customers for her work.
            <Text>${name} bounced from table to table taking orders and recommending items to help you make more money.</Text>
            <Text>She's very good at this. You saw her several times today carrying out two orders at a time.</Text>
            <Text>
                When placing drink on the table she got slapped on the ass by one of the customers.
                ${name} scolded them in a flirty way, saying that this kind of behavior could get them kicked out by
                the security and that she didn't want to lose her favorite customers.
                The client apologies, assuring her that he didn't mean any harm.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Knowing the menu paid off for ${name}.
                After hearing the order she advised a more expensive option.
                Customers went for it and enjoyed their stay. Happy with the good advice they left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text>Memorizing the menu and prices has paid off for ${name}.</Text>
            <Text>${name} is a town favourite and knows most of the patrons by name and what they order.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and gets praised by the customers often.
            <Text Condition="Abnormally Large Boobs|Giant Juggs|Massive Melons|Titanic Tits" Priority="0">
                The patrons love being served by ${name}.
                Due to her skill at this job and the chance to stare at her legendary boobs.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Busty Boobs|Big Boobs|Giant Juggs" Priority="0">
                The patrons love being served by ${name}.
                Due to her skill at this job and the chance to stare at her Big Boobs.
            </Text>
            <Text>${name} didn't mess up any order this shift. Keeping the patrons happy.</Text>
            <Text>One mishap today. A customer got away without paying!</Text>
            <Text>She spends her shift greeting customers and showing them to their tables.</Text>
            <Text>
                Being confident in her skill, ${name} didn't make a single mistake today.
                She also earned some tips from happy customers.
            </Text>
            <Text>Having a slow shift, she mostly gossip with other staff members.</Text>
            <Text>Ensuring that every table was served, tired ${name} took a five minute breather.</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} had some regulars come in.
                She knows there order by heart and put it in as soon as she seen them walk in making them happy.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.
            <Text>
                ${name} forgot to take an order to a table for over an hour.  But they were in a forgiving mood and stuck around.
            </Text>
            <Text>Trying her best, ${name} made few mistakes but otherwise she had a pleasant day.</Text>
            <Text>She tripped over her own shoelaces when carrying out an expensive order!</Text>
            <Text>
                Taking orders without mistakes and getting drinks to the tables not spilling a single drop from them.
                Today was a good day for ${name}.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                When placing drink on the table she got slapped on the ass by one of the customers.
                ${name} didn't ignore that and called him names.
                Her behavior left the clients stunned for a moment.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} spent her shift on cleaning duty.
                Mopping the floor, wiping tables and ensuring that the bathrooms were accessible.
                She did a decent job.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} sneezed in an order she had just sat down on a table.
                Needless to say the patron was mad and left.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.
            <Text>${name} wrote down the wrong orders for a few patrons resulting in them leaving.</Text>
            <Text>
                After being asked for the fourth time to repeat his order,
                the irritated customer left your facility.
                ${name} clearly isn't very good at this job.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Giving back change to a customer, ${name} made an error calculating the amount in favor of the client.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Holding the tray firmly in her hands, ${name} successfully delivered the order to designated table.
                She was so nervous and focused on not failing this time,
                that she jumped scared when the customer thanked her.
            </Text>
            <Text>${name} really hates this job. She used every opportunity to take a break.</Text>
            <Text>Still learning to do her job, ${name} gets some orders wrong making a lot of people really angry.</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} sneezed in an order she had just sat down on a table.
                Needless to say the patron was mad and left.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.
            <Text>
                ${name} was taking orders to the wrong tables and
                letting a lot of people walk out without paying their tab.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was presenting the ordered dish when she sneezed in it.
                The outraged customer demanded a new serving, that he got on the house.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The tray slipped from ${name}'s hand right in front of the patron.
                Causing her to get yelled at for being bad at her job.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Trying her best, ${name} focused on not screwing up today.
                Surprisingly she managed not to fail at one of her appointed tasks today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                After picking up a tray full of drinks from the bar, ${name} tried to bring it to the table.
                Her attempt failed when she slipped on wet floor that she mopped a minute ago.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was slacking on the job spending most of her shift chatting with other staff members.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} spilled food all over the place and mixed orders up constantly.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="post-work-text">
            <Text Condition="Beauty>=85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Clumsy" Chance="15" Updates="Wages-=25">
                Her clumsy nature cause her to spill food on a customer resulting in them storming off without paying.
            </Text>

            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="10">
                <Text Condition="Performance<130" Updates="Tips-=10" >
                    Her pessimistic mood depressed the customers making them tip less.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>120" Updates="Tips+=10" >
                    ${name} was in a poor mood so the patrons gave her a bigger tip to try and cheer her up.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="10">
                <Text Condition="Performance<130" Updates="Tips-=10" >
                    ${name} was in a cheerful mood but the patrons thought she needed to work more on her services.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>120" Updates="Tips+=10" >
                    Her optimistic mood made patrons cheer up increasing the amount they tip.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Psychic" Chance="20">
                <Text Updates="Tips+=20" >
                    She used her Psychic skills to know exactly what the patrons wanted to order making
                    them happy and increasing her tips.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=20" >
                    ${name} uses her psychic abilities to her advantage.
                    She knows when a customer is thinking about dessert or another bottle of wine,
                    and shows up just in time with the perfect recommendation.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Assassin" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance>140">
                    A patron pissed her off but she just gave them a death stare and walked away.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance<150" Updates="Tips-=50;Wages-=50" >
                    A patron pissed her off and using her Assassin skills she killed him before even thinking about it
                    resulting in patrons storming out without paying.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Horrific Scars" Chance="15">
                <Text Condition="Performance<160">
                    A patron gasped at her Horrific Scars making her uneasy. But they didn't feel sorry for her.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>150" Updates="Tips+=25">
                    A patron gasped at her Horrific Scars making her sad.
                    Feeling bad about it as she did a wonderful job they left a good tip.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Text Condition="Fleet Of Foot" Chance="30">
                ${name} is fast on her feet, and makes great time navigating from table to table.
                She is able to serve almost twice as many customers in her shift.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Dojikko" Chance="35">
                ${name} accidentally sends a tray of plates crashing to the floor,
                drawing the eyes of the entire restaurant to her.
                She smiles and sighs with such cuteness that everyone just laughs,
                and the customer whose dish splattered all over the tiles grins and says
                he would be happy to wait for a replacement, and that it could happen to anyone.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Herbalism>40" Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Added a little something extra to the patrons order to spice it up.
                They enjoyed it greatly and she received some nice tips.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
