<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="CP">
    <Description>
        She will clean up the filmed scenes. One Purifier can process at most 3 scenes per week.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Confidence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Refinement" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Magic" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Crafting" Weight="1"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="5" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Magic" Weight="1" />
        <Skill Name="Crafting" Weight="1" />
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" />
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="no-crew">
            <Text>There was no crew to film the scene, so ${name} took the day off.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="no-actress">
            <Text>There were no actresses to film, so ${name} took the day off.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to work as a crystal purifier today.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} was assigned to work as a Crystal Purifier.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>
                Her skill with movie crystals, together with her deep understanding of colour and contrast allowed
                her to transform the scene into a masterpiece. Truly an outstanding work in post-production.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>
                She preserves the recordings with great skill, and is able to perform some touch-ups that make the
                scenes look even better.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>
                She knows how to preserve the recording, and has the skill to edit them further in post-production.
                What ${name} is lacking is the experience on where to edit and how to touch up things in a more subtle
                way.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>
                She managed to preserve the recording more or less in the same state as the original film.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>
                She managed to preserve the recordings in a storage crystal, though the image is somewhat distorted
                in places.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>
                Seeing the cracked movie crystal, you decide that ${name} probably should never again be left
                unsupervised with the footage. It is a wonder that there is still something left of the scene.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>