<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Scrt">
    <Description>
        She will be an escort.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Skill="Anal" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="BDSM" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Beastiality" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Footjob" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Group" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Handjob" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Lesbian" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="NormalSex" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="OralSex" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Strip" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="TittySex" Weight="1"/>

        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="6"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="6"/>

        <Mod>work.escort</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="aggressive">
            <Text>
                ${name} has some particularly aggressive tendencies that make her a poor choice for patrons seeking polite conversation.
                Even if she carries a conversation well, the undercurrent of restrained hostility will detract from her performance.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="bimbo">
            <Text>
                ${name} is a complete ditz.
                Her repertoire of conversation is limited to her favorite dresses and her many powerful feelings on makeup brands.
                This will stymie her abilities as an escort, no matter how well she does otherwise.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="shy">
            <Text>
                ${name} is very shy with new people. For a job that requires meeting with new people constantly,
                this is a bad trait to possess.
                Her nervousness will translate into some awkward conversational moments, no matter how great her charisma is.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="retarded">
            <Text>
                ${name} is retarded, and this is a natural obstacle to most conversations.
                For those men that do not want a prolonged conversation on her favorite colors or a description of her last "poopy,"
                which is the vast majority of men, she may have some trouble as an escort.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="psychic">
            <Text>
                ${name} has some psychic abilities, meaning she has a natural advantage in conversation.
                She knows what the client likes and can avoid the subjects that he dislikes.
                This may come in very handy.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="charming">
            <Text>
                ${name} is very personable and charming.
                Conversations with her will be easy, and this gives her an advantage as an escort.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular">
            <Text>
                ${name} has been requested by a regular client,
                a man who has called on her before and now is willing to pay extra for a special assignation.
                His new boss has asked the client out for a double date with the client's girlfriend and his own wife so he can get to know his new employee better.
                The problem is that the client does not have a girlfriend.
                ${name} is to arrive at a local restaurant, equipped with a suitable dress and pair of shoes,
                ready to chat amiably.
                The client sends a list of written details about their "shared relationship" for her to memorize.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular.well-prepared">
            <Text>
                ${name} immediately delves into the customer biography on the client and does some independent research on him.
                She memorizes the list in total detail, and even scopes out the places where they are supposed to have met and had their previous dates.
                She arrives at the door of the restaurant at the exact appointed time.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular.prepared">
            <Text>
                ${name} arrives at the door of the bustling downtown restaurant just in time. She actually arrived half an hour ago,
                and has spent her time scoping out the restaurant and its patrons and contemplating conversation topics.
                She read the biography that your escort clients are obligated to provide,
                and knows enough details about her repeat client and their fictional relationship that she is ready to make it appear believable.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular.on-time">
            <Text>
                ${name} arrives just on time, with a relatively good understanding of the details of their shared "relationship"
                so she can appear as if she really is his girlfriend.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular.late">
            <Text>
                ${name} arrives ten minutes late, dressed suitably and mulling over conversation topics.
                She knows her lateness will probably upset him,
                but she has at least reviewed some of the list of details of their "relationship" so that she does not need to completely improvise.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="regular.unprepared">
            <Text>
                ${name} arrives at the restaurant half an hour late, barely groomed and with minimal efforts to make herself presentable.
                She has not memorized anything on the list and will just have to improvise the details of their "relationship".
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
