<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Feed">
    <Description>
        She will work in a soup kitchen.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Intelligence" Weight="1" />
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1" />
        <Factor Skill="Service" Weight="2" />
        <Mod>work.communityservice</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <Stat Name="Intelligence" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Skill Name="Service" Weight="1" Max="70"/>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to work during the ${shift} shift.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked feeding the poor.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be perfect at this.
            <Text>
                Today ${name} was managing the kitchen giving orders to other cooks and checking the quality of their work.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was helping in the kitchen. Her task was to stir-fry vegetables. One word: Perfection. Food that she prepared was great!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Being done with the main dish earlier, ${name} decided to bake cookies for desert!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Excellent dish! Some world class chefs should learn from ${name}!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} knife skill is impressive. She's cutting precisely and really fast, almost like a machine.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by people for her work.
            <Text>
                ${name} is in charge of the cooking for several weeks now.
                You could swear that the population of rodents and small animals in the area went down.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                While preparing for today's cooking, ${name} noticed that one of the crucial ingredients is missing.
                She manage to change the menu and fully use available ingredients.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She speedily served all in line at the food counter. All the portions handed out were equal.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Preparing something new she mixed up the proportions from the recipe. The outcome tasted great!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was helping in the kitchen. Her task was to prepare the souse for today's meatballs.
                The texture and flavor was top notch.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and gets praised by people often.
            <Text>While cooking she used everything that was in the kitchen. Nothing was wasted.</Text>
            <Text>While cooking she accidentally sneezed into the pot. Luckily nobody saw that.</Text>
            <Text>"${name} was helping in the kitchen.
                Her task was to carve the meat.
                Smile on her face that appear while doing this, was somehow scary and disturbing.</Text>
            <Text>${name} was doing the dishes. Most of them "survived" and will be used next time.</Text>
            <Text>She spent her shift at the food counter without any trouble.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.
            <Text>Her cooking isn't very good. But You probably would risk serving the prepared dish to a dog.</Text>
            <Text>Today she was assign as the cook. Not being able to focus on the task at hand, she overcooked the pasta.</Text>
            <Text>She served all in line at the food counter. Some portions were smaller than others.</Text>
            <Text>${name} was helping in the kitchen. Her task was to make a salad. She manage to do this much.</Text>
            <Text>When walking with a pile of clean dished she slipped and fall. All the plates got broken.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.
            <Text>Today she was assign as the cook. Meatballs that she prepared could be used as lethal projectiles.</Text>
            <Text>${name} was doing the dishes.
                Let's say it would be a lot quicker to throw them all right away,
                then wait for her to break so many during this simple chore.
            </Text>
            <Text>While cooking she burned two brand new pots!</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was helping in the kitchen. Her task was to dice the carrots.
                Surely the carrots were cut, but to called them diced would be an exaggeration.
            </Text>
            <Text>Just wanting to serve the food fast to end her shift. She did a sloppy job at the food counter.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.
            <Text>While preparing ingredients for the soup she almost cut off her hand!</Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} was helping in the kitchen. Her task was to peel the potatoes.
                The peels were thick and had a lot of the vegetable left on them. What a waste!
            </Text>
            <Text>Today she was assigned as the cook. The thing that she created hardly could be called food.</Text>
            <Text>
                Today she was assigned to work at the food counter.
                While handing out food she served different portions to people in line.
            </Text>
            <Text>Being assigned to the food counter, she put a sign "self serving" and went out.</Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
