<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Cage">
    <Description>
        She will fight against other girls. Dangerous.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Skill="Combat" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Magic" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Constitution" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Agility" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Fame" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>

        <Mod>work.fightarena</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Combat" Weight="3"/>
        <Skill Name="Magic" Weight="1"/>
        <Stat Name="Constitution" Weight="1"/>
        <Stat Name="Agility" Weight="1"/>

        <GainTrait Trait="Tough" Threshold="20" Action="COMBAT">
            She has become pretty Tough from all of the fights she's been in.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Aggressive" Threshold="60" Action="COMBAT">
            She is getting rather Aggressive from her enjoyment of combat.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Fleet of Foot" Threshold="30" Action="COMBAT">
            She is getting rather fast from all the fighting.
        </GainTrait>
        <LoseTrait Trait="Fragile" Threshold="75" Action="COMBAT">
            ${name} has had to heal from so many injuries you can't say she is Fragile anymore.
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to fight during the ${shift} shift.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="victory">
            <Text Condition="Exhibitionist">
                As she enjoys showing off her body, ${name} lets her opponent cut away her already-skimpy clothing,
                ending her match all but naked - but victorious.  Many of the patrons seem to enjoy the show.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sadistic">
                As the match draws to a close, ${name} stops trying to win and simply toys with her opponent,
                practically torturing her in front of the audience.  Many patrons disapprove, although a few respond favorably.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Dominatrix">
                ${name}'s verbal abuse, along with her combat prowess, lead to a dramatic defeat of her opponent,
                although her behavior towards the loser disappoints many patrons.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Brawler">
                ${name}'s preference for grappling and clinch-fighting throws her opponent off-balance and gives her an easy,
                if somewhat boring, victory.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Flight">
                Being able to fly is an almost-unfair advantage that most opponents can't counter.
                Thanks to that, ${name} wins handily.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Assassin">
                Utilizing a no-rules, victory-at-any-cost combat style,
                ${name} won a decisive victory over her orthodox opponent.
                This was not unnoticed by some people in the audience.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Masochist">
                ${name}'s cries of joy and outright pleasure upon being injured distract her opponent,
                and the pain-loving girl comes back from apparent defeat to achieve a dramatic victory.
                Despite her many injuries, she smiles happily as she thanks her opponent for the match.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Magic > 50 ^ skill:Combat < 50">
                ${name}'s powerful magic demonstrates precisely why mages are feared by many.
                She even manages to look good while doing it!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Magic > 75 ^ skill:Combat > 75">
                Having mastered both weapons and sorcery,
                ${name} is a nearly unstoppable force of nature in the Arena,
                easily dispatching opponents who focus on one branch of combat over the other.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} won her fight.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="defeat">
            <Text Condition="Exhibitionist">
                As she enjoys showing off her body, ${name} lets her opponent cut away her already-skimpy clothing,
                but either because of her lack of skill or just bad luck, she takes a real hit and is defeated.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sadistic">
                ${name} tries to torment her opponent,
                but her overconfidence leads to a stunning defeat when the other fighter feigns injury.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Flight">
                ${name} was unable to leverage her greater maneuverability
                and yielded the match after being forced to the ground.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Masochist">
                Overwhelmed by pleasure, ${name} is unable to defend herself from her opponent and is easily defeated.
                After the match ends, she begs the other fighter for another match - 'just like this one.'
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Magic > 50 ^ skill:Combat < 50">
                Lacking the physical prowess to hold her opponent off while she readies her spells,
                ${name} is quickly defeated by her opponent.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Magic > 75 ^ skill:Combat > 75">
                You can't believe, ${name} lost. With her skill in combat and magic you thought her unbeatable.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She lost the fight.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="draw">
            <Text>
                The fight ended in a draw.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
