<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FLes">
    <Description>
        She will do a lesbian scene.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Lesbian" Weight="1"/>
        <Mod>work.pornstar</Mod>
        <Trait Name="Lesbian" Value="10" />
        <Trait Name="Straight" Value="-10" />
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Lesbian" Weight="1" Max="75"/>

        <GainTrait Trait="Porn Star" Threshold="70" Action="PORNSTAR">
            She has performed in enough sex scenes that she has become a well known Porn Star.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Fake Orgasm Expert" Threshold="50" Action="SEX">
            She has become quite the Faker.
        </GainTrait>
        <LoseTrait Trait="Chaste" Threshold="20" Action="PORNSTAR">
            She has been filmed having sex so often that she is no longer Chaste.
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config PrimaryAction="PORNSTAR" SecondaryAction="SEX" CanBeForced="1">
        <LustInfluence Amount="25" SkillMin="20" BaseValue="5" Skill="Lesbian" />
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as an actress filming lesbian scenes.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>${name} doesn't care who she works with. She always gives a Perfect scene.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is an amazing actress. Even though she very much prefers fucking men, as soon
                as the director yells "Action!" she starts eating out her co-star with such vigor that you
                fear she might not be able to walk for the next hours. This is going to be one hell of a scene.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>${name} pleased her lover in amazing ways.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} really prefers dick over pussy, but she is a competent actress and does not let it show in
                the scene. In fact, the end result is a pretty great movie clip.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>${name} gave several good orgasm's to her lover.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                Despite being Straight, ${name} gave a decent performance in this Lesbian
                scene.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>${name} didn't care for her assigned actress, she did an ok job.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is only interested in men, and is not quite able to hide her revulsion
                while performing with another woman. Still, with some clever editing a halfway
                decent scene could be produced.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>${name} visually wasn't interested in her lover at all. Terrible scene.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                ${name} is as Straight as they come, and her disgust with this Lesbian scene can
                be clearly seen on camera. The result is pretty terrible. Maybe you should find a
                girl who is more into this.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>${name} was totally horrible today.  She was scorned for hours by the entire crew.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="disobey.free">
            <Text>${name} refused to perform in a Lesbian scene today.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Straight">
                "Eww, I'm not gonna do it with a woman", ${name} exclaims before leaving the set.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.nice">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to perform in an Lesbian scene today. Nice guy that you are, you let her be.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.neutral">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to perform in an Lesbian scene today. "That's not how I wanted this to be," you say,
                "but I've got bills to pay. Tie her up!"
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.evil">
            <Text>
                "No, I'm not doing this!", ${name} complains. Ignoring her pleading, your studio crew roughly ties her up. "It seems
                like a lesson in obedience is in order here", you say as you hand a gigantic dildo to the
                other actress actor. Turning to her with an evil grin on you face, you add "No foreplay, no lube!"
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="forced-filming">
            <Text Condition="Performance>100">
                Given ${name}'s rather 'unenthusiastic' performance, the scene turned out decent enough.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit<60">
                ${name} is just laying there, totally unresponsive except for a few whimpers and cries.
                Not a good scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit>=60">
                Despite being tied up, ${name} managed to hurt the other actress. Needless to say, the scene
                turned out rather bad.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<50">
                While tying her up made it possible to film this scene, the result looks so bad that maybe you should
                have just sent her to the dungeon instead.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
