<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FOrl">
    <Description>
        She will perform in an oral sex scene.
    </Description>
    <Performance Modifier="">
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="OralSex" Weight="1"/>
    </Performance>
    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="OralSex" Weight="1" />
        <GainTrait Trait="Porn Star" Threshold="80" Action="WORKMOVIE">
            She has performed in enough sex scenes that she has become a well known Porn Star.
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as an actress filming oral scenes.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to give head on film today.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>
            The lucky guy came uncontrollably, damn near passing out in pleasure as ${name} expertly sucked him dry.
            She savoured the cum in her mouth, rolling it around her lips and tongue before finally swallowing it down.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            ${name} sucked off her man like a pro - not once breaking eye-contact - and was rewarded with
            <Text Condition="Cum Addict" Priority="1">
                a mouthful of semen. She kept her lips clamped to his cock to the last,
                thirstily swallowing down every drop of hot cum.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                a mouthful of semen. She kept her lips clamped to his cock to the last,
                thirstily swallowing down every drop of hot cum.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                an explosion of cum in her face. As she licked his penis clean,
                she rubbed cum around her skin and licked it off her fingers.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>${name} gave a fairly pleasant blowjob, and ended up glazed in hot cum.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>${name} gave a passable blowjob, but in the end the actor had to finish himself off, splatting cum on her face.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>
                It was a pretty awkward and uncomfortable scene,
                with the actor not getting any kind of pleasure from her clumsy, toothy attempts.
                In the end he gave up and simply wanked in her face, but even then she dodged at the last moment,
                ruining that scene too.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>
                After the fourth time she 'snagged' the actor on her tooth, he cursed and stormed off set.
                Your goons saved the day by pinning her down wanking on her face one-by-one.
                Overall it's a terrible scene.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
