<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="FGrp">
    <Description>
        She will film a group sex scene.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Group" Weight="1"/>
        <Mod>work.pornstar</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Group" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Skill Name="Constitution" Weight="1" Max="40"/>

        <GainTrait Trait="Porn Star" Threshold="80" Action="PORNSTAR">
            She has performed in enough sex scenes that she has become a well known Porn Star.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Fake Orgasm Expert" Threshold="50" Action="SEX">
            She has become quite the Faker.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Slut" Threshold="80" Action="SEX" Event="2">
            ${name} has turned into quite a Slut.
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config PrimaryAction="PORNSTAR" SecondaryAction="SEX" CanBeForced="1">
        <LustInfluence Amount="25" SkillMin="33" BaseValue="15" Skill="Group" />
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} starred in an orgy scene today.</Text>
            <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac^Porn Star">
                ${name} worked in a scene where she tried to set a new record by taking part in a $[25|35|69] men gangbang.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="disobey.free">
            <Text>${name} refused to do an Orgy on film today.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.nice">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to do an Orgy on film today. Nice guy that you are, you let her be.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.neutral">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to perform in an Orgy scene today. "That's not how I wanted this to be," you say,
                "but I've got bills to pay. Boys, tie her up!" Seeing her terrified expression, you call out to her co-stars:
                "Be gentle with her, will ya!".
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="disobey.slave.evil">
            <Text>
                "No, I'm not doing this!", ${name} complains. Ignoring her pleading, your men roughly tie her up.
                "It seems like a lesson in obedience is in order here", you say as you produce a pair of nipple clamps.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="pre-work-event">
            <Text Condition="Lolita" Chance="50">
                With such a young looking girl on the cover, this movie is simply sure to sell out.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Cute" Chance="50">
                Such a cute girl doing her best to handle the rough ponding her co-stars gave her will surely make a few hearts skip a beat.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Fragile|Delicate" Chance="50">
                This will be somewhat rough for her. Some people find that hot though.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="post-work-event">
            <Text Condition="Bimbo^Performance<150" Chance="50">
                Her performance couldn't be considered acting.
                She just enjoyed a good dicking with a blissfully stupid smile on her face.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Natural Pheromones" Chance="50">
                Her scent drove the actors mad with lust. They went at it harder and wilder than the director had ordered.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Fast Orgasms" Chance="50">
                She came the second she got two dicks inside her.
                That was the first of many orgasms.
                She barely remembered her own name by the end of the scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Great Arse" Chance="50">
                Her ass jiggling with each thrust was a sight to behold.
                The camera mage made sure to capture its wiggly glory in slow motion.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Plump" Chance="50">
                She sure offered a lot of meat to work with.
                The wet and fleshy sound she made with each thrust is sure to drive the audience wild.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Cum Addict" Chance="50">
                She insisted that her co-stars collect their semen in a cup for her to drink at the end of the scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Succubus" Chance="50">
                After the camera stopped running, she grabbed two actors and had another round with them.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>${name} filmed a perfect orgy scene.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>${name} filmed a great orgy scene.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>${name} did alright today, hopefully she will be better in the future.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>The good thing about filming an orgy scene: Even if the main girl is rather unskilled,
                there is enough action going on for the end result to be decent. </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>${name} performed in an orgy scene. The result looked awful.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>This has to be the worst orgy ever recorded on film.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="forced-filming">
            <Text Condition="Performance>100">
                Given ${name}'s rather 'unenthusiastic' performance, the scene turned out decent enough.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit<60">
                ${name} is just laying there, totally unresponsive except for a few whimpers and cries.
                Not a good scene.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<125^stat:Spirit>=60">
                Despite being tied up, ${name} managed to hurt one of the other actors. Needless to say, the scene
                turned out rather bad.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Performance<50">
                While tying her up made it possible to film this scene, the result looks so bad that maybe you should
                have just sent her to the dungeon instead.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
