<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Msus">
    <Description>
        She will give massages to the customers.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <!-- intel and agility for smarts and speed to cheat; cust service, performance to bluff/cheat, and a bit of magic for 'luck'-->
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Strength" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Service" Weight="3"/>
        <Factor Skill="Medicine" Weight="3"/>
        <Mod>work.masseuse</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <Skill Name="Medicine" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Skill Name="Service" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="155" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="95" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="55" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="15" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="-5" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="-15" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to massage customers in your brothel to${shift}</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked massaging customers.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be the perfect masseuse she never goes too hard but never too soft.
            She knows just what to do and the customers can't get enough of her.

            <Text Updates="Tips+=20">
                Being asked to perfume more sensual massage, ${name} massage the customer with her breasts for some extra coin.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Every man left ${name}'s room with a wide smile.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A client wanted ${name} to focus on a tight region.
                Doing as he asked, she left him with a boner.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She is well known and has a steady base of faithful customers.
            </Text>
            <Text Updates="Tips+=20">
                ${name} hands are the best thing that could touch a man.
                Customers left big tips after getting a massage from her.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always finding new ways to please the customer.

            <Text Updates="Earnings+=15">
                Today she used some new oils. The customers liked them and paid some extra for the service.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She certainly knows how and where to press on a man's body.
                Today, customer moans were heard in the corridor.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Trying a new technique, ${name} performed a massage with her feet.
                The customer really liked it and suggested she should put this on the regular menu.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her customer wanted something more than the usual service.
                She declined and banned him from her customers list.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Knowing most of masseur's techniques, she is one of the best.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and knows a few tricks to drive the customers wild.

            <Text>
                {name} helped a customer with a really painful back pain.
                The man bowed several times, thanking her for the treatment.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She's making fewer mistakes with every day and earning good money.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                When massaging a customer, she had a pleasant conversation with him, leaving a very good impression.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She certainly knows how to do her job and is getting better at it every day.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A female customer requested a face massage. ${name} managed to meet her expectations.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.

            <Text>
                Maybe she isn't the best, but at least she won't kill anyone.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She got the job done. No complaints were noted.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She was good. A few of ${name}'s customers praised her.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She made few mistakes, but managed not to hurt anyone today.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Only a few customers came today. She didn't earn much.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.

            <Text>
                ${name} almost killed a customer today!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Her performance was bad. The customer left a complaint and didn't pay for the service.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Thing that she did today could be called a backrub, not a massage.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She argued with a client and kicked him out on the street wearing only a towel around his waist.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Not knowing what to do, she tried her best and failed.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.

            <Text>
                ${name} massaged a client. He could barely walk out after her service.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Getting kicked by a horse or getting a massage from ${name}.
                Equally deadly but the first you could get for free.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A loud scream was heard in your building shortly after ${name} started her shift.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Not having any experience in this kind of work she fails miserably.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She tries to massage a client in the best way she knows.
                After ten minutes he leaves without paying and frustrated.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="after-work">
            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance<175" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    Her pessimism made her unadventurous. The customers were unimpressed and the tips were lower.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} performed well despite her mood.
                    The customers enjoy the darker, sultry nature of her sex shows.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance<175" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    ${name} smiled far too much to look seductive.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} showed endless energy, agility and enthusiasm as she rucked around the stage.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Clumsy" Chance="15">
                Her clumsy nature caused her to lose one of her "toys" up a hole.
                <Text Updates="Tips+=10" Chance="50">
                    She put on a damn sexy show of getting it back out.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips-=10">
                    She panicked and ran off stage to go find a doctor.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Chance="20" Condition="stat:Beauty>85" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="10" Condition="Cat Girl" Updates="Tips+=15">
                ${name} is able to clean herself like a cat. Customers are amazed as this pussy-cat
                spreads her legs wide and licks her own cunt right there on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="10" Condition="Masochist" Updates="Tips+=15">
                <!-- TODO Health -->
                ${name} invites a few customers to punish her on stage. They happily agree to spank and whip her.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>