<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Nurs">
    <Description>
        Will help the doctor and heal sick people.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Skill="Medicine" Weight="3"/>
        <Factor Stat="Intelligence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>

        <!-- good traits -->
        <Trait Name="Charismatic" Value="20"/>
        <Trait Name="Sexy Air" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Cool Person" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Cute" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Charming" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Nerd" Value="15"/>
        <Trait Name="Quick Learner" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Psychic" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Doctor" Value="40"/>
        <Trait Name="Goddess" Value="10"/> <!-- might be able to heal people easier.. they are a goddess after all -->
        <Trait Name="Optimist" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Priestess" Value="10"/>

        <!-- bad traits -->
        <Trait Name="Dependant" Value="-50"/>
        <Trait Name="Clumsy" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Aggressive" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Nervous" Value="-30"/>
        <Trait Name="Retarded" Value="-50"/>
        <Trait Name="Meek" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Mind Fucked" Value="-50"/>
        <Trait Name="Pessimist" Value="-10"/>
        <Trait Name="Sadistic" Value="-20"/>
        <Trait Name="Zombie" Value="-100"/>

        <Trait Name="One Arm" Value="-40"/>
        <Trait Name="One Foot" Value="-40"/>
        <Trait Name="One Hand" Value="-30"/>
        <Trait Name="One Leg" Value="-60"/>
        <Trait Name="No Arms" Value="-150"/>
        <Trait Name="No Feet" Value="-60"/>
        <Trait Name="No Hands" Value="-90"/>
        <Trait Name="No Legs" Value="-150"/>
        <Trait Name="Blind" Value="-75"/>
        <Trait Name="Deaf" Value="-15"/>
        <Trait Name="Retarded" Value="-60"/>
        <Trait Name="Smoker" Value="-10"/> <!-- would need smoke breaks -->

        <Trait Name="Former Addict" Value="-25"/> <!-- not good idea to let former addict around all those drugs -->
        <Trait Name="Alcoholic" Value="-25"/>
        <Trait Name="Fairy Dust Addict" Value="-25"/>
        <Trait Name="Shroud Addict" Value="-25"/>
        <Trait Name="Viras Blood Addict" Value="-25"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="10" Skill="2">
        <Skill Name="Medicine" Weight="2"/>
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1" />
        <Stat Name="Intelligence" Weight="1" />
        <GainTrait Trait="Charismatic" Threshold="60" Action="WORKNURSE">
            Dealing with patients and talking with them about their problems has made ${name} more Charismatic.
        </GainTrait>
        <LoseTrait Trait="Nervous" Threshold="30" Action="WORKNURSE">
            ${name} seems to finally be getting over her shyness. She's not always so Nervous anymore.
        </LoseTrait>
    </Gains>
    
    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as a nurse.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be the perfect nurse, patients go on and on about her and always come to see her when she works.

            <Text>Just the sight of ${name} brings happiness to the patients. She is a blessing to the entire ward.</Text>
            <Text>Today the knowledge and swift reaction from ${name} saved a patient's life!</Text>
            <Text>She was doing her routine with a wide, beautiful smile and humming a pleasant tune.</Text>
            <Text>Her work is her life. She finds fulfillment in every day working in the clinic.</Text>
            <Text>She spent her day supervising new nurses, showing them how to do the work properly and answering tons of questions.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised for her work by the patients.

            <Text>${name} is good at her work. Besides helping patients, she gave some pointers to younger, less experience coworkers.</Text>
            <Text>${name} was on her feet all day long. She was really tired but also felt fulfilled.</Text>
            <Text>She managed to calm a patient before a major surgery.</Text>
            <Text>When assisting in a surgery, she knew what tool will be needed, before the surgeon called for them.</Text>
            <Text>${name} is really committed to her job as a nurse. She's starting to feel enjoyment after every hard worked day.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and gets praised by the patients often.

            <Text>She made one of the patients heart beat dangerously high, while leaning over his face to rearrange the pillow.</Text>
            <Text>${name} made her rounds and spend the rest of the day chatting with other staff members.</Text>
            <Text>When giving medicine to the patient, ${name} noticed that the dosage for one of them was wrong. She corrected her mistake immediately.</Text>
            <Text>Today she was assigned to the surgery room. She learned something new.</Text>
            <Text>It was a busy day for ${name}, but she manage to get through it without any slip-ups.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.

            <Text>She accidentally gave a patient the wrong dosage of their drugs! Fortunately she understated them.</Text>
            <Text>${name} made a mistake while changing bandages of one of her patients. The head nurse scolded her.</Text>
            <Text>She spent her shift following the doctor and learning more about the job.</Text>
            <Text>She slapped an older patient for groping her ass! Good thing that the doctor was near to help him stay alive!</Text>
            <Group>
                When giving a sponge bath to one of male patients she accidentally aroused his manhood
                <Text Condition="Shy|Meek">. Ashamed from the sight, she ran out the room!</Text>
                <Text>but it didn't bother her any.</Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.

            <Text>When prepping her patient before a mayor surgery she described all possible bad outcomes forgetting to mentioning the low risk percentage and good sides of this treatment.</Text>
            <Text>${name} took the temperature of all patients in her block with the same thermometer without sterilizing it!</Text>
            <Text>She got scolded today by the doctor for laughing at the patients that came in for liposuction about their weight.</Text>
            <Text>Being responsible for utilizing today's medical waste, ${name} just flushed them down the toilet.</Text>
            <Text>She spend most of her shift snoozing in the basement medical supply storage.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.
            <Text>Some could say that her technique of drawing blood is the same way people play pin the tail on the donkey.</Text>
            <Text>Sponge bath, skinning someone alive, no difference for ${name}.</Text>
            <Text>${name} covered her mouth while sneezing several times. After that she went to assist in the ongoing surgery without changing her gloves!</Text>
            <Text>While assisting the doctor, ${name} giggled when the patient was telling about their health problems.</Text>
            <Text>${name} fainted at the first sight of blood. She wasn't helpful today.</Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
