<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="SWtr">
    <Description>
        She will bring drinks and food to the customers at the tables while dressed in lingerie or fetish costumes.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Brewing" Weight="1"/>

        <Mod>work.sleazywaitress</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Clumsy" Threshold="30" Action="WORKCLUB">
            It took her breaking hundreds of dishes, and just as many reprimands, but ${name} has finally stopped being so Clumsy.
        </LoseTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Charming" Threshold="70" Action="WORKCLUB">
            ${name} has been flirting with customers to try to get better tips. Enough practice at it has made her quite Charming.
        </GainTrait>
        <Skill Name="Service" Weight="3" />
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="155" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="95" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="55" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="15" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="-5" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="-15" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>
                ${name} is instructed to work at your sleazy restaurant as a waitress.
                She is informed that the customers here want good service,
                but they chose this place because of the promise of attractive women in skimpy clothing.
                If she wants to be successful, she will need to impress them with her body as well as her service.

                She worked as a waitress in the strip club.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to be a waitress for the creeps in your strip club to${shift}</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be the perfect waitress customers go on and on about her and always come to see her when she works.
            <Text>
                ${name} is amazing as a waitress, and dances about the room from table to table keeping all the customers satisfied.
                She recalls their orders by perfect memory, watches everyone to make sure they have everything they want,
                and appears as if by magic the moment anyone places a menu back on the table or returns their fork to the plate.
                Her sexy body keeps everyone thinking about her long after she walks away.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} does a great job, and her memorization of the menu and the specials,
                paired with her timely service and polite demeanor,
                pays dividends as she moves from table to table collecting orders.
                The patrons are pleased, and while ${name} knows better than to interrupt anyone while they are eating,
                the customers have no complaints when she is forced to do so.
                She walks with just the right sexy strut that she is a welcome sight whenever she appears.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by the customers for her work.
            <Text>
                ${name} is a very good waitress, and collects the orders promptly and politely.
                She has almost everything on the menu memorized and can speak knowledgeably about the beer list and customer favorites.
                She occasionally spends too much time at each table or appears while customers are still considering their orders,
                but this does not seriously detract from her service,
                and the patrons who enjoy her extra attention flirt with her constantly.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} impresses the patrons with her efficiency, politeness, and knowledge.
                She deftly deters the patrons away from dishes that are not perfected,
                and also from dishes that are too inexpensive.
                She talks a number of customers into ordering a more expensive special,
                and they are all happy with the results, especially as she hovers long and low over them,
                brushing them repeatedly with her breasts as she sets it on the table.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and gets praised by the customers often.
            <Text>
                ${name} provides satisfactory service. She tends to show up too early,
                and occasionally the customers feel rushed,
                but ${name} is nevertheless polite and courteous and everyone is generally pleased with her work.
                She needs to learn more about the menu items and the specials,
                and her flirtations with the customers feel forced and unnatural, but all in all, her work is good.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is fairly good as a waitress.
                She is attentive and prompt, and while she has to write all the orders down in order not to forget,
                the customers are not too put out by her efforts.
                She does not understand the cooks' capabilities well enough to steer customers away from poorer dishes,
                but she is good enough at flirting with them and occasionally grinding against them that they are distracted from the meal.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.
            <Text>
                ${name} manages to get all the food ordered and delivered,
                but that is the extent of her skills.
                Her unease at this job translates into customers that feel rushed to order sooner than they would like,
                and her inability to speak with knowledge about the menu items and specials leads them to make hasty and usually inexpensive selections.
                When she tries to bend low and give them a good view of her tits as they order,
                it ends up looking awkward and forced. The patrons are satisfied by her work, but only just.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is still learning how to be a decent waitress.
                She is able to get the right food to the right patron on time,
                but it is clear that she is still training in her job.
                Her attempts at grinding her ass against them are badly timed and usually come across as clumsiness rather than flirtation,
                and the customers show limited patience while she asks them to repeat their orders as she writes everything down.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.
            <Text>
                ${name} is not very good at working as a waitress.
                She forgets orders and has to return to the tables for clarification regularly.
                Some patrons get the wrong meal, and a few choose to leave without paying rather than wait for her to place the corrected order.
                She stumbles over the menu options and her flirtatious comments sound like a terrible actress rehearsing even worse lines.
                The customers are not very pleased with her work, and her tips reflect this.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} barely makes it through her shift without running every customer out of the restaurant.
                Her skills need a lot of work. She asks patrons for their orders before they even pick up the menu,
                and rather than giving them time to look it over and select,
                she stands there staring until they place the order.
                She tries to make up for this by "gently" brushing her tits against their heads when she adjusts something on the table,
                but it ends up being a weird boob mash in their ears.
                Most patrons find this very unnerving, but it would probably be forgiven if she brought them the right orders.
                She does not, usually. Some patrons walk out, promising that they will tell their friends about the poor service.
                Almost nobody tips her.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.
            <Text>
                ${name} is really bad at serving as a waitress.
                Awful, really. She hassles customers for food orders, interrupts them constantly while they eat,
                and constantly screws up their order.
                She makes practically no effort to flirt or entice the customers with her body.
                The kitchen is constantly compelled to send complimentary food out to cover for her poor service,
                but most customers are not so easily placated and deride ${name} to her face.
                They leave, promising that they will never come back. Nobody tips her.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} understands nothing about being a waitress. The menu confuses her,
                the specials are completely outside her understanding,
                and she has no idea how to use her body to her advantage.
                Those customers that stick around after her terrible initial service are not very surprised to find
                that a completely different meal than the one they ordered finds its way to their table.
                She hovers over them while they eat, clearly waiting for them to finish and pay so she can bus the table.
                Nobody tips her, and most tell her that they will not come back again as long as she works here.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="event.post">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>99" Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=50">
                ${name} looked absolutely stunning during her shift and was unable to hide it.
                Instead of her ass or tits, the patrons couldn't glue their eyes off her face,
                and spent a lot more than usual on tipping her.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Charisma>85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=35">
                ${name} surprised a couple of gentlemen discussing some complicated issue by her
                insightful comments when she was taking her order.
                They decided her words were worth a heavy tip.
            </Text>

            <Group Condition="Clumsy" Chance="15" Updates="Earnings-=25">
                <Text>
                    Her clumsy nature cause her to spill food on a customer resulting in them storming off without paying.
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    ${name} is clumsy, which is not a great attribute for someone that carries food for others all day.
                    All the customers are jarred to hear a pile of plates come crashing down to the floor,
                    as ${name} sheepishly stares at the heap of broken dishes and scattered food.
                    A customer is forced to wait while she apologizes and places a new order.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} was in a poor mood so the patrons gave her a bigger tip to try and cheer her up.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    Her pessimistic mood depressed the customers making them tip less.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    Her optimistic mood made patrons cheer up increasing the amount they tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    ${name} was in a cheerful mood but the patrons thought she needed to work more on her services.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Great Figure" Chance="25">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    Not only does she have an amazing figure but she is also an amazing waitress the patrons really love her and her tips prove it.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125">
                    ${name}'s amazing figure wasn't enough to keep the patrons happy when her service was so bad.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Exhibitionist|stat:Dignity<=-20" Chance="20">
                <Text Updates="Tips+=20">
                    During her shift, ${name} deliberately dropped the pen she uses to write down orders in front of one of the customers.
                    Exploiting her skimpy outfit,
                    she made sure to bend over to pick it up in a way that allowed her to directly flash her butt on the sitting client's eye level.
                    This earned her an extra tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips+=30">
                    An inebriated patron said half-jokingly to ${name} that he'll leave a heavy tip if she takes his order while sitting on his lap.
                    Much to his surprise, ${name} was almost too eager to comply, sitting directly on his crotch instead,
                    making sure to grind her butt into it.
                    The customer lived up to his word and ${name} left the table with some extra cash.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Priority="-1"/>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
