<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="SBmd">
    <Description>
        She will staff the bar and serve drinks while dressed in lingerie or fetish costumes.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Brewing" Weight="1"/>

        <Mod>work.barmaid</Mod>

        <Trait Name="Charismatic" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Sexy Air" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Psychic" Value="10"/>
        <Trait Name="Great Figure" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Great Arse" Value="5"/>
        <Trait Name="Shy" Value="-10"/>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="20" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Nervous" Threshold="20" Action="WORKBAR">
            ${name} seems to finally be getting over her shyness. She's not always so Nervous anymore.
        </LoseTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Charismatic" Threshold="60" Action="WORKBAR">
            Dealing with customers at the bar and talking with them about their problems has made ${name} more Charismatic.
        </GainTrait>
        <Skill Name="Service" Weight="3" />
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Brewing" Weight="1" />
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="155" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="95" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="55" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="15" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="-5" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="-15" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as a bartender in the strip club.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to be a barmaid in your strip club to${shift}</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="event.nympho">
            <Text>
                ${name} dragged one of the less sober clients outside into a back alley and ordered him to fuck her senseless against a wall.
                After the deed, the poor fellow passed out and ${name} returned to her job as if nothing happened.
            </Text>
            <Text Updates="Tips+=50">
                ${name} spotted a relatively good-looking guy walking into the bathroom alone.
                She followed him inside, and as he tried to exit the bathroom stall, he got pushed back in by her.
                ${name} didn't waste any time and in a matter of seconds was vigorously fucking the client.
                After the deed, the client made sure ${name} had a pretty hefty wad of money stuck behind her skirt.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            <Text>She must be the perfect bar tender customers go on and on about her and always come to see her when she works.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.great">
            <Text>She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by the customers for her work.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.good">
            <Text>She's good at this job and gets praised by the customers often.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.ok">
            <Text>She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.bad">
            <Text>She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.worst">
            <Text>She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="event.grab-boob">
            A drunken patron decide to grab ${name}'s boob.
            <Text Condition="Meek">
                She was shocked and didn't react. The man molested her for a few minutes!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Tough">
                She knocked him out! You could swear that she knocked a couple of his teeth out too!
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Your Daughter">
                She screamed: "Do you know who my dad is? He will have your head for this!"
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Your Wife">
                She screamed: "Do you know who my husband is? He will have your head for this!"
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:PCLove > 80">
                She screamed do you know who my love is? He will have your head for this!
            </Text>
            <Text>
                She screamed and shook his hand off.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="event.post">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>99" Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=50">
                ${name} looked absolutely stunning during her shift and was unable to hide it.
                Instead of her ass or tits, the patrons couldn't glue their eyes off her face,
                and spent a lot more than usual on tipping her.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="stat:Charisma>85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=35">
                ${name} surprised a couple of gentlemen discussing some complicated issue by her
                insightful comments when she was taking her order.
                They decided her words were worth a heavy tip.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} was in a poor mood so the patrons gave her a bigger tip to try and cheer her up.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    Her pessimistic mood depressed the customers making them tip less.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    Her optimistic mood made patrons cheer up increasing the amount they tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    ${name} was in a cheerful mood but the patrons thought she needed to work more on her services.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Priority="-1"/>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
