<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="SSrp">
    <Description>
        She will strip on the tables and stage for the customers.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Strip" Weight="2"/>

        <Mod>work.stripper</Mod>

        <!--
        The original code had a fame bonus and a pregnancy malus
        -->
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="3">
        <LoseTrait Trait="Nervous" Threshold="20" Action="WORKSTRIP">
            ${name} has had so many people see her naked she is no longer nervous about anything.
        </LoseTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Sexy Air" Threshold="80" Action="WORKSTRIP">
            ${name} has been stripping and having to be sexy for so long she now reeks of sexyness.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Exhibitionist" Threshold="60" Action="WORKSTRIP">
            ${name} has been stripping for so long she loves to be naked now.
        </GainTrait>
        <Stat Name="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="2" />
        <Skill Name="Strip" Weight="2" />
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" Max="33"/>
    </Gains>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as a stripper in the club.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>"${name} refused to strip off in front of the creeps in your club to${shift}</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="event.nympho">
            <Text>
                ${name} dragged one of the less sober clients outside into a back alley and ordered him to fuck her senseless against a wall.
                After the deed, the poor fellow passed out and ${name} returned to her job as if nothing happened.
            </Text>
            <Text Updates="Tips+=50">
                ${name} spotted a relatively good-looking guy walking into the bathroom alone.
                She followed him inside, and as he tried to exit the bathroom stall, he got pushed back in by her.
                ${name} didn't waste any time and in a matter of seconds was vigorously fucking the client.
                After the deed, the client made sure ${name} had a pretty hefty wad of money stuck behind her skirt.
            </Text>
        </Message>


        <Message Name="event.post">
            <Text Condition="stat:Beauty>85" Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Clumsy" Chance="5" Updates="Earnings-=15">
                Her clumsy nature caused her to slide off the pole causing her to have to stop stripping for a few hours.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} was in a poor mood so the patrons gave her a bigger tip to try and cheer her up.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    Her pessimistic mood depressed the customers making them tip less.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    Her optimistic mood made patrons cheer up increasing the amount they tip.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    ${name} was in a cheerful mood but the patrons thought she needed to work more on her services.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Great Figure" Chance="20">
                <Text Condition="Performance > 125" Updates="Tips+=15">
                    ${name}'s great figure draws a large crowed to the stage and her skill at stripping makes them pay up to see the show up close.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance <= 125" Updates="Tips+=5">
                    ${name} has a great figure so she draws a few extra patrons even if she needed to work more on her stripping.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Priority="-1"/>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="lapdance.great">
            ${name} doesn't have to try to sell private dances the patrons beg her to buy one off her.
            <Text Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=200">
                She sold a champagne dance.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="15" Updates="Tips+=100">
                She sold a shower dance.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=125">
                She was able to sell a few VIP dances.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="20" Updates="Tips+=50">
                  She sold a VIP dance.
            </Text>
            <Text Priority="-1" Updates="Tips+=40">
                She sold several lap dances.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="lapdance.good">
            ${name}'s skill at selling private dances is impressive.
            <Text Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=50">
                She convinced a patron to buy a shower dance.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="15" Updates="Tips+=45">
                Sold a VIP dance to a patron.
            </Text>
            <Text Priority="-1" Updates="Tips+=40">
                "Sold a few lap dance.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="lapdance.ok">
            ${name} tried to sell private dances
            <Text Chance="5" Updates="Tips+=33">
                and was able to sell a VIP dance against all odds.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="15" Updates="Tips+=15">
                and was able to sell a lap dance.
            </Text>
            <Text Priority="-1">
                "but wasn't able to sell any.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="lapdance.bad">
            <Text>
                ${name} doesn't seem to understand the real money in stripping is selling private dances.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
