<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Prtc">
    <Description>
        She will train either alone or with others to improve her skills.
    </Description>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to practice her skills.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="refuse.forced">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to practice her skills, so Mistress ${mistress} had some of your goons tie
                her up and whipped her for her disobedience. Next time she'll think twice before
                disobeying ${mistress}.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="no-mistress">
            <Text>
                There was no Mistress available to train ${name}, so she tried practicing her skills on her own.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="lack-of-skill">
            <Text>
                ${mistress}'s attempts to improve ${name}'s ${skill} skills are ineffective because her own abilities
                are too low.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.NormalSex">
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex < 20">
                Noticing ${name}'s utter lack of experience, ${mistress} decides to start the lessons gently. She
                produces a small dildo. "You just lie back and relax", she tells ${name} as she slowly inserts it,
                "you need to get used to the sensation."
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 15 ^ skill:NormalSex < 35">
                Given ${name}'s relative inexperience, ${mistress} decides to bring in $[Felix][Alejandro][Myles][Wilmer],
                one of your more soft-hearted boys. "You just lie back and relax", she tells ${name}, "he is going to
                do all the work."

                In the beginning, ${name} shows all the enthusiasm of a dead fish, but after some time ${mistress}
                notices that she starts moving her hips and moaning softly. Seems like some progress after all.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Normal Sex training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Strip">
            <Text>
                Strip training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.BDSM">
            <Text>
                BDSM training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Beastiality">
            <Text>
                Bestiality training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Handjob">
            <Text>
                Handjob training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Footjob">
            <Text>
                Footjob training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.TittySex">
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex < 33">
                <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Petite Breasts" Priority="1">
                    "Well, this is gonna be a challenge!" ${mistress} sighs as she looks at ${name}'s flat chest.
                    But that's why I'm here.

                    They spent the lesson trying to figure out how to use what passes for ${name}'s boobs to achieve
                    something resembling a titty fuck. The results were rather disappointing.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Abnormally Large Boobs|Giant Juggs|Massive Melons|Titanic Tits" Priority="1">
                    ${mistress} had ${name} give a titjob to one of the guards.
                    "I would have though someone as well equipped as you would have no trouble with this",
                    ${mistress} criticises, "but this was just bad!"
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    "Just press your tits together, $[Otto][Bruno][Albert] here will do the rest", ${mistress}
                    instructs in exasperation. She hadn't expected this to be so difficult. It appears that
                    some more training sessions will be necessary before ${name} can give a passable titjob.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 33 ^ skill:TittySex < 66">
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex medium skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 60 ^ skill:TittySex < 85">
                <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Petite Breasts" Priority="1">
                    ${mistress} brought one of your guards to the training session:
                    "Now ${name}, show me what you've learned and give him a nice titty fuck"
                    "Really, her?", the guard looks sceptically at ${name}'s chest.

                    An hour later, satiated, he looks incredulously back at ${name} as he is leaving the room.
                    "Sorry I ever doubted you."
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex high skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 80">
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex very high skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.OralSex">
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex < 20">
                "Let's practice your cock-sucking", ${mistress} says as she calls over one of your gang members.
                He starts wincing almost immediately after ${name} takes his still flaccid dick in her mouth.
                "Oh dear!". ${mistress} sends him away with an apology. "I guess we need to start with the basics."
                She pulls out a small dildo: "Maybe you should practice with something that doesn't feel pain".

                By the end of the lesson, ${name} almost manages to suck the dildo without scraping her teeth.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 15 ^ skill:OralSex < 30">
                "Let's practice your cock-sucking", ${mistress} says as she calls over one of your gang members.
                ${name} looks at his flaccid penis quizzically. "You've got to caress it gently, before the real
                work starts", the Mistress explains. She demonstrates this by running her tongue along the length
                of his shaft while softly cupping his balls. "Go on, ${name}, it's your turn now!".
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 25 ^ skill:OralSex < 50">
                ${mistress} brings one of your gang members to the lesson. "I think you know the basics of
                giving a blowjob, now it's time to practice." ${name} spent the next few hours sucking his cock.
                Her jaw was aching, but she dare not complain under ${mistress}'s stern gaze.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 45 ^ skill:OralSex < 60">
                "It is time you learnt the finer points of giving an unforgettable blowjob", ${mistress} says to
                ${name}. "Eye contact, your posture and demeanour, what you do with your hands, all this is important
                if you want him to leave you a large tip. Let me show you how it's done."

                Even after many trials, ${name} still seems to do something wrong. When she caresses his balls, she
                keeps looking at her hands, when she keeps her posture her sucking is lacklustre at best. A lot if
                practice is still in order.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 55 ^ skill:OralSex < 70">
                "It is time you learnt the finer points of giving an unforgettable blowjob", ${mistress} says to
                ${name}. "Eye contact, your posture and demeanour, what you do with your hands, all this is important
                if you want him to leave you a large tip. Let me show you how it's done."

                ${name} does a decent job. The guard that ${mistress} brought for practice just after his shift ended
                does not seem to mind the overtime.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 66 ^ skill:OralSex < 85">
                "Well, that was fast", comments ${mistress} as the guard she brought for practice shoots his load down
                ${name}'s throat. "But remember, you are paid by the hour! Let's try again, but this time, keep him
                excited for a while before you make him cum."

                ${name} starts working her magic again, and soon feels the next guy tensing up. She takes his
                $[dick][cock] out of her mouth and shoots a questioning glance at ${mistress}. Just in that moment,
                he splurges his load, catching her in the eye. ${mistress} chuckles: "Well, looks like we need to
                practice this some more. Should be good for the morale of the boys, eh"
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 80">
                "I'm not sure there is much more I can teach you." ${mistress} tells ${name}. "Your cock-sucking seems
                to be on-point." After a moment of thinking, she leaves the room, and soon reenters with a rather burly
                man. "This is $[Olaf][Corb][Doug][Ralph]. He has trouble finding a woman that can handle someone as
                well-equipped as him. You do like a challenge, don't you?"
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Performance">
            <Text>
                Performance training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Anal">
            <Text Condition="skill:Anal < 20">
                Noticing ${name}'s utter lack of experience, ${mistress} decides to start the lessons gently.
                She takes out the smallest dildo she could find, and proceeds to apply generous amounts of lube.
                "This may be a bit uncomfortable at first, but I'm sure you'll come to love it", she tells ${name}
                as she starts to slowly probe her asshole.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Anal training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Group">
            <Text>
                Anal training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Lesbian">
            <Text>
                Lesbian training.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="skill:Lesbian > 80">
                <Text>
                    ${mistress} sits down, spreads her legs, and guides ${name}'s head between her thighs. As ${name}
                    dutifully begins to explore her pussy with her tongue, she leans back with a sigh. If only all of
                    her assignments could be this enjoyable.
                </Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
