<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="Prtc">
    <Description>
        She will train either alone or with others to improve her skills.
    </Description>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to practice her skills.</Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="refuse.forced">
            <Text>
                ${name} refused to practice her skills, so Mistress ${mistress} had some of your goons tie
                her up and whipped her for her disobedience. Next time she'll think twice before
                disobeying ${mistress}.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="no-mistress">
            <Text>
                There was no Mistress available to train ${name}, so she tried practicing her skills on her own.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="lack-of-skill">
            <Text>
                ${mistress}'s attempts to improve ${name}'s ${skill} skills are ineffective because her own abilities
                are too low.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.NormalSex">
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex < 20">
                Noticing ${name}'s utter lack of experience, ${mistress} decides to start the lessons gently. She
                produces a small dildo. "You just lie back and relax", she tells ${name} as she slowly inserts it,
                "you need to get used to the sensation."
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 15 ^ skill:NormalSex < 35">
                Given ${name}'s relative inexperience, ${mistress} decides to bring in $[Felix][Alejandro][Myles][Wilmer],
                one of your more soft-hearted boys. "You just lie back and relax", she tells ${name}, "he is going to
                do all the work."

                In the beginning, ${name} shows all the enthusiasm of a dead fish, but after some time ${mistress}
                notices that she starts moving her hips and moaning softly. Seems like some progress after all.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 30 ^ skill:NormalSex < 45">
                "Well, if your body were cold, I think you would make a necrophile quite happy. But for anyone else,
                you have to show a bit more activity than a corpse!", ${mistress} criticises after seeing ${name} in
                "action". "The boys are probably too enthusiastic, doing all the work for you. Here, lets try this."

                She shows ${name} an anatomically rather accurate dildo and pushes the tip into her pussy. "Now you
                have to do the actual fucking. Come on, show me what you've got!"
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 40 ^ skill:NormalSex < 66">
                ${mistress} decides that it is time for ${name} to learn other positions than just missionary.
                "Today, you are going to practice the $[Cowgirl][Doggy style][Reverse Cowgirl][Leap Frog] position."

                After hours of sweaty exercise, ${mistress} is sure that ${name} has made some progress.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 60 ^ skill:NormalSex < 85">
                ${name} is already quite good, so ${mistress} decides that it is time to teach her
                the finer points of professional intercourse: How to make sure he doesn't cum too fast,
                what to say afterwards, etc.

                ${mistress} brought one of your goons as a practice partner. The lucky guy has never been
                happier with his choice of career.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:NormalSex > 80">
                ${name} is already basically a sex goddess, so ${mistress} just fetched some of your goons.
                This will boost morale greatly, and makes sure ${name} doesn't get rusty. And some of the more
                athletic positions definitely also count as cardio.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Strip">
            <Text Condition="Clumsy^skill:Strip < 30">
                While practicing a strip dance with ${mistress}, Clumsy ${name} managed to get her panties
                caught in her heels and fell. After patching her up, ${mistress} decided to end the lesson
                for the day.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="skill:Strip < 20">
                <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac|Exhibitionist">
                    ${name} is so eager to get out of her clothes that ${mistress} spends the entire lesson trying to
                    slow her down so that the "strip tease" can take longer than 10 seconds. So far, she hasn't been
                    very successful at this.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy">
                    ${name} is extremely uncomfortable with the thought of getting naked in front of strangers.
                    For now, ${mistress} allows her to keep on her underwear. Even still, ${name} is shivering
                    uncontrollably at the end of the lesson.
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    "Wow, that was the least sexy strip tease I've ever seen", ${mistress} complains once ${name}
                    has finished. ${mistress} decides to start very simple and lets ${name} ignore the pole for now,
                    and just asks her to remove her clothing slowly. It looks very awkward.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:Strip > 15 ^ skill:Strip < 30">
                <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy">
                    ${name} is still very uncomfortable with the thought of getting naked in front of strangers, but
                    she must learn to cope with this. ${mistress} orders her to strip, but she immediately tries
                    to cover herself with her hands as soon as her bra comes off. ${mistress} gently moves ${name}'s
                    hands away. "See, this isn't so bad"
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac|Exhibitionist">
                    ${name} is so too eager to get out of her clothes quickly. ${mistress} explains to her that is she
                    strips more slowly, her audience will admire her body even more and become more aroused. The idea
                    clearly appeals to ${name}, and on her next try she deliberately slows down her movements. While
                    it looks a bit stiff and awkward, this is a major improvement.
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    ${mistress} ties to get ${name} to make sensual movements while removing her clothing. However,
                    her success in this is rather limited.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:Strip > 25 ^ skill:Strip < 45">
                <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy">
                    Even though ${name} is clearly uncomfortable with the situation, she manages to present ${mistress}
                    with a fairly decent strip tease.

                    "Good, we're finally getting somewhere. I think it is time you practiced in front of an actual
                    audience."

                    "A..Audience?", ${name} stammers, her face suddenly very pale.

                    Mistress calls into the hallway: "Mark, Pete, come in here, there is something I want you to see!"
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    By now, ${name} has learned to remove her clothing in a way that could, by a generous definition
                    of the word, be considered alluring. Thus ${mistress} thinks it is time to have her practice some
                    basic exercises at the pole.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:Strip > 40 ^ skill:Strip < 66">
                <Text Condition="Chaste|Shy">
                    ${name} feels uncomfortable when stripping in front of an audience, but has learned to hide
                    this very well. ${mistress} is pleased with her progress, and starts instructing her on how
                    to include the pole in her performance.
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    ${name} knows all the basic moves of a stripper, so ${mistress} focuses her instruction on
                    some finer points. "A successful stripper has to interact with her audience, then she'll be able
                    to sell private lap dances. This is were the real money is", she explains while she has ${name}
                    practice eye contact with the goons she invited for the lesson.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:Strip > 60 ^ skill:Strip < 85">
                <Text>
                    ${name} is a fairly skillful stripper, so ${mistress} is confident that she will attract the interest
                    of some patrons once you let her perform in one of your establishments. She will need to transform
                    that interest into monetary gain, and therefore ${mistress} has her practicing lap dances with a few
                    of you staff who are currently on break.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Condition="skill:Strip>80">
                ${mistress} has ${name} practice some challenging acrobatic moves on the stripper pole. Even for someone
                as skilled as ${name}, they are no easy feat, and she has to repeat them several times until ${mistress}
                is happy with the results.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.BDSM">
            <Group Condition="skill:BDSM < 20">
                ${name} has no experience with BDSM, so ${mistress} decides to start her training slowly.
                <Text>
                    ${name} is blindfolded and tied naked to the bed.
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    She has ${name} wear a $[ball|ring|bit|cleave] gag for the duration of the lesson. She has to
                    get used to this.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:BDSM < 30 ^ skill:BDSM > 10">
                <Text>
                    ${mistress} is trying to get ${name} used to some light BDSM play. She orders her
                    to lie on her stomach, and proceeds to spank her ass until the the skin turns bright red.
                    She takes out a flogger, and ${name} -- with panic in her eyes -- begs her to stop. Given
                    ${name}'s lack of BDSM experience, ${mistress} decides to take it easy. She lets ${name}
                    beg for a few more minutes, but then puts the flogger away.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac|stat:Libido>90">
                    "I really don't like pain, but just the thought of getting fucked while tied up makes me wet",
                    ${name} proclaims as ${mistress} announces that they will do some BDSM training today.
                    "I can arrange that", she smirks, and five minutes later ${name} is cuffed to the bed and a
                    well-equipped man enters the room. ${name} looks at him hungrily, but her attention is captured
                    by ${mistress} who produces a pair of nipple clamps. "Oh, I forgot to mention - you're not getting
                    fucked without these. And I'm only putting them on if you beg for it!"

                    "Please" "Please what?" "Please put the clamps on my nipples." "Are you sure? I though you didn't
                    like pain" "Please, mistress, I want the clamps!"
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text>
                BDSM training.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Masochist ^ skill:BDSM > 95" Chance="5">
                Masochistic ${girl} begs ${mistress} to be allowed to devise her own punishments.

                A few minutes later, she is tied spread-eagle to the floor. Not just on the hard, cold stone tiles,
                no, she had somebody spread small pebbles there beforehand. Her original idea had been hot coals, but
                ${mistress} forbade everything that had a chance of leaving permanent scars. She is wearing an inflatable
                gag pumped up to the maximum, prying her stuffed mouth open and pressing against the back of her throat.
                Strong clamps are pinching her nipples, connected with twine to her big toes, and additional clothespins
                are placed on her breasts and stomach.

                ${mistress} starts by caning ${girl}'s feet, first lightly, but rapidly increasing the intensity. Soon
                the smacks can be heard in the hallway, and her spasming feet cause sharp tugs at her nipples. Finally,
                she foot too strongly and with a muffled scream the left nipple clamp is pulled free. "Let's get the
                other one, too", ${mistress} announces and focuses her attention on the right foot...

                After an hour, ${mistress} ends the session, worrying that any more might seriously harm ${girl}, who is
                lying dazed on the floor, a mixture of agony and bliss on her face. Her boobs are covered in dried wax,
                her stomach is shining brightly red from the flogging and her legs are covered in dark welts that the
                whip has left. But perhaps most impressive is the large puddle between her legs, fluid still dripping
                from her glistening pussy.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Beastiality">
            <Text>
                Bestiality training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Handjob">
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob < 20">
                After a very painful accident when practicing with one of your
                guys, ${mistress} decides that for now, ${name} should give
                handjobs only to inanimate objects.

                Once she manages to stroke a dildo in a way that does not look
                like it would cause serious physical injury, maybe she can try again.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob > 15 ^ skill:Handjob < 33">
                ${mistress} picks one of your goons and orders ${name} to
                give him a handjob. Going by the expression on your goon's face,
                she is not doing a very good job.

                In the end, ${mistress} decides to demonstrate how it is done and
                finishes him off.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob > 28 ^ skill:Handjob < 50">
                ${mistress} picks one of your goons and orders ${name} to
                give him a handjob. She is experienced enough to get him to
                cum quickly, but the performance is probably not very memorable.

                ${mistress} uses the rest of the lesson to explain to ${name} that
                her goal is not to make him cum as quickly as possible, but to have
                him enjoy the experience so much that he will visit again and pay
                more money.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob > 45 ^ skill:Handjob < 66">
                ${name} knows how to give decent handjobs, so ${mistress} decides
                to give her some more advanced instructions. She has ${name}
                practice varying her speed, rhythm, and movements. The guard who
                was brought in for practice certainly appreciated ${mistress}'s
                command to give his balls some love too.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob > 60 ^ skill:Handjob < 85">
                ${name} knows how to give good handjobs, so ${mistress} decides
                to give her some more advanced instructions. Left-handed, right-handed,
                both hands, fast, slow, only the tip or along the entire shaft, ${mistress}
                has her practice all sorts of variations. She also makes sure that ${name}
                uses the rest of her body to properly tease the lucky guy.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Handjob > 80">
                ${name} is an expert at giving handjobs, so ${mistress} decides to
                present her with a real challenge today. One of your guards, only called
                $[Limp Leo|Soft Sven|Flaccid Frederick] by the others, has certain performance
                problems. Yet after a few minutes, ${name} is pumping away on his rock-hard cock,
                and soon he splurges a huge load all over her.

                "I guess you've been really saving that, eh", ${mistress} comments dryly, "Good work, ${name}!".
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Footjob">
            <Text>
                Footjob training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.TittySex">
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex < 33">
                <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Petite Breasts" Priority="1">
                    "Well, this is gonna be a challenge!" ${mistress} sighs as she looks at ${name}'s flat chest.
                    But that's why I'm here.

                    They spent the lesson trying to figure out how to use what passes for ${name}'s boobs to achieve
                    something resembling a titty fuck. The results were rather disappointing.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Abnormally Large Boobs|Giant Juggs|Massive Melons|Titanic Tits" Priority="1">
                    ${mistress} had ${name} give a titjob to one of the guards.
                    "I would have though someone as well equipped as you would have no trouble with this",
                    ${mistress} criticises, "but this was just bad!"
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    "Just press your tits together, $[Otto][Bruno][Albert] here will do the rest", ${mistress}
                    instructs in exasperation. She hadn't expected this to be so difficult. It appears that
                    some more training sessions will be necessary before ${name} can give a passable titjob.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 33 ^ skill:TittySex < 66">
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex medium skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 60 ^ skill:TittySex < 85">
                <Text Condition="Flat Chest|Petite Breasts" Priority="1">
                    ${mistress} brought one of your guards to the training session:
                    "Now ${name}, show me what you've learned and give him a nice titty fuck"
                    "Really, her?", the guard looks sceptically at ${name}'s chest.

                    An hour later, satiated, he looks incredulously back at ${name} as he is leaving the room.
                    "Sorry I ever doubted you."
                </Text>
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex high skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="skill:TittySex > 80">
                <Text>
                    Titty Sex very high skill
                </Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.OralSex">
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex < 20">
                "Let's practice your cock-sucking", ${mistress} says as she calls over one of your gang members.
                He starts wincing almost immediately after ${name} takes his still flaccid dick in her mouth.
                "Oh dear!". ${mistress} sends him away with an apology. "I guess we need to start with the basics."
                She pulls out a small dildo: "Maybe you should practice with something that doesn't feel pain".

                By the end of the lesson, ${name} almost manages to suck the dildo without scraping her teeth.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 15 ^ skill:OralSex < 30">
                "Let's practice your cock-sucking", ${mistress} says as she calls over one of your gang members.
                ${name} looks at his flaccid penis quizzically. "You've got to caress it gently, before the real
                work starts", the Mistress explains. She demonstrates this by running her tongue along the length
                of his shaft while softly cupping his balls. "Go on, ${name}, it's your turn now!".
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 25 ^ skill:OralSex < 50">
                ${mistress} brings one of your gang members to the lesson. "I think you know the basics of
                giving a blowjob, now it's time to practice." ${name} spent the next few hours sucking his cock.
                Her jaw was aching, but she dare not complain under ${mistress}'s stern gaze.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 45 ^ skill:OralSex < 60">
                "It is time you learnt the finer points of giving an unforgettable blowjob", ${mistress} says to
                ${name}. "Eye contact, your posture and demeanour, what you do with your hands, all this is important
                if you want him to leave you a large tip. Let me show you how it's done."

                Even after many trials, ${name} still seems to do something wrong. When she caresses his balls, she
                keeps looking at her hands, when she keeps her posture her sucking is lacklustre at best. A lot if
                practice is still in order.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 55 ^ skill:OralSex < 70">
                "It is time you learnt the finer points of giving an unforgettable blowjob", ${mistress} says to
                ${name}. "Eye contact, your posture and demeanour, what you do with your hands, all this is important
                if you want him to leave you a large tip. Let me show you how it's done."

                ${name} does a decent job. The guard that ${mistress} brought for practice just after his shift ended
                does not seem to mind the overtime.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 66 ^ skill:OralSex < 85">
                "Well, that was fast", comments ${mistress} as the guard she brought for practice shoots his load down
                ${name}'s throat. "But remember, you are paid by the hour! Let's try again, but this time, keep him
                excited for a while before you make him cum."

                ${name} starts working her magic again, and soon feels the next guy tensing up. She takes his
                $[dick][cock] out of her mouth and shoots a questioning glance at ${mistress}. Just in that moment,
                he splurges his load, catching her in the eye. ${mistress} chuckles: "Well, looks like we need to
                practice this some more. Should be good for the morale of the boys, eh"
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:OralSex > 80">
                "I'm not sure there is much more I can teach you." ${mistress} tells ${name}. "Your cock-sucking seems
                to be on-point." After a moment of thinking, she leaves the room, and soon reenters with a rather burly
                man. "This is $[Olaf][Corb][Doug][Ralph]. He has trouble finding a woman that can handle someone as
                well-equipped as him. You do like a challenge, don't you?"
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Performance">
            <Text>
                Performance training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Anal">
            <Text Condition="skill:Anal < 20">
                Noticing ${name}'s utter lack of experience, ${mistress} decides to start the lessons gently.
                She takes out the smallest dildo she could find, and proceeds to apply generous amounts of lube.
                "This may be a bit uncomfortable at first, but I'm sure you'll come to love it", she tells ${name}
                as she starts to slowly probe her asshole.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Anal>15 ^ skill:Anal<30">
                ${mistress} hands ${name} a string of anal beads and a bottle of lubricant.
                "We're doing some stretching exercises today."
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Anal>25 ^ skill:Anal<40">
                "I'll go and fetch Jonny", ${mistress} tells {girl} as she hands her some lube and a butt-plug.
                "You'd better start stretching your anus, otherwise this will be painful".

                Despite her preparations, it hurt when Jonny slowly pushed in his dick. He started fucking her gently,
                and while she still thought it a bit uncomfortable, after a while the pain subsided. Her training
                is starting to pay off.
            </Text>
            <Group Condition="skill:Anal>35 ^ skill:Anal<66">
                ${name} has some anal experience, and ${mistress} decides that today they are going to
                increase the intensity of the training a bit. She calls in three of your goons, who spent
                the next few hours taking turns fucking ${name} in the ass.
                <Text Condition="skill:Anal < 55">
                    After the lesson ends, you can see ${name} wincing as she sits down.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="skill:Anal > 45">
                    She is a little sore after the lesson, but overall her training seems to pay off nicely.
                </Text>
            </Group>

            <Text Condition="skill:Anal > 55 ^ skill:Anal < 75">
                ${name} has enough anal experience for ${mistress} to start the more advanced training.
                Instead of just passively getting penetrated, she now has to take an active part. While
                she does so in the beginning, after a short while the man ends up doing all the work.

                "Thanks, $[Peter|Bob|Steve], you did good work, but I think for this lesson I need someone a little
                less cooperative." Mistress takes out a dildo and mounts it on the wall. "Now, get on all fours and
                fuck that", ${mistress} instructs, "There will be no slacking off now"
            </Text>

            <Text Condition="skill:Anal > 70 ^ skill:Anal <= 90">
                "Your anal sex skills are pretty good", ${mistress} tells ${name}, "but I think we still can improve
                the variety you provide. Lets practice the
                $[Lotus|Cowgirl|Piledriver|Turtle|Leap Frog|Bodyguard|Burning Man|Cross|Pump|Bulldog|See Saw|Jockey]
                position today.
            </Text>

            <Text Condition="skill:Anal>90">
                ${mistress} presents an enormous butt-plug to ${name}. "I've heard you like a challenge",
                she says, "so go on and impress me!"

                It took ${name} more than half an hour and a copious amount of spit, but finally, she managed to
                insert the device up to the base into her ass.

                "It seems like I need to get an even bigger one specifically manufactured for you. I really did not
                think this monstrosity would fit. Well done, you can take the rest of the day off."
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Group">
            <Text>
                Group training.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="train.Lesbian">
            <Text>
                Lesbian training.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Lesbian < 25^Straight">
                "I don't care if you think this is disgusting, when a client wants you to lick her pussy, you will
                do it! And I will make sure that you do it so well that once you are finished, they will have trouble
                remembering their name!", ${mistress} shouts after ${name} insisted that she is Straight and won't have
                sex with a woman.

                Not trusting ${name}, ${mistress} calls in another one of your girls as training subject. "We'll start
                slowly, then. Make her come! This time, I allow you to use your fingers".

                What followed was a rather uncomfortable experience for the unfortunate practice partner.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Lesbian < 20">
                Given ${name}'s utter lack of skill in pleasuring women, ${mistress} decided that the best course of
                action was to have her figure out how to pleasure herself first. But after watching ${name} poke
                her vagina for half an hour without much signs of even getting aroused, ${mistress} opts for a demonstration
                instead.

                "Just lay back and relax, but try to pay attention to what I do", she says, before starting to caress
                ${name}'s pussy gently with her fingers. After a minute or so, ${name}'s breathing starts to quicken,
                and ${mistress} begins finger-fucking her in earnest. Just when ${name} is ready to cum, she stops.
                "The rest", she says with a hint of sadism in her smile, "the rest you have to do yourself".
            </Text>

            <Group Condition="skill:Lesbian > 80">
                <Text>
                    ${mistress} sits down, spreads her legs, and guides ${name}'s head between her thighs. As ${name}
                    dutifully begins to explore her pussy with her tongue, she leans back with a sigh. If only all of
                    her assignments could be this enjoyable.
                </Text>
            </Group>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>
