<!DOCTYPE Job SYSTEM "job.dtd">
<Job ShortName="XXXE">
    <Description>
        She will provide sexual entertainment to the customers.
    </Description>

    <Performance>
        <!-- intel and agility for smarts and speed to cheat; cust service, performance to bluff/cheat, and a bit of magic for 'luck'-->
        <Factor Stat="Beauty" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Skill="Performance" Weight="2"/>
        <Factor Stat="Charisma" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Confidence" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Skill="Strip" Weight="1"/>
        <Factor Stat="Libido" Weight="1"/>
        <!-- TODO malus for pregnant -->
        <Mod>work.hallxxx</Mod>
    </Performance>

    <Gains XP="15" Skill="2">
        <Stat Name="Confidence" Weight="1" Max="50" />
        <Skill Name="Performance" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <Skill Name="Strip" Weight="1" Max="50"/>
        <GainTrait Trait="Nymphomaniac" Threshold="75" Action="WORKSTRIP">
            Having to perform sexual entertainment for patrons every day has made ${name} quite the nympho.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Exhibitionist" Threshold="50" Action="WORKSTRIP">
            Performing sexual entertainment for strangers every day has made ${name} quite keen to show off her sexuality.
        </GainTrait>
        <GainTrait Trait="Sexy Air" Threshold="80" Action="WORKSTRIP" Chance="25" MinPerformance="140">
            ${name} has been having to be sexy for so long she now reeks sexiness.
        </GainTrait>
    </Gains>

    <Config>
        <WageFunction>
            <Point Performance="245" Wages="155" />
            <Point Performance="185" Wages="95" />
            <Point Performance="145" Wages="55" />
            <Point Performance="100" Wages="15" />
            <Point Performance="70" Wages="-5" />
            <Point Performance="0" Wages="-15" />
        </WageFunction>
    </Config>

    <Messages>
        <Message Name="refuse">
            <Text>${name} refused to provide sexual entertainment in the gambling hall to${shift}</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work">
            <Text>${name} worked as a sexual entertainer in the gambling hall.</Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.perfect">
            She must be the perfect entertainer customers go on and on about her and always come to see her when she works.

            <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac" Chance="33">
                ${name} could do this all day with a genuine smile on her face,
                pussy dripping onto the stained boards beneath her legs.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="33">
                ${name} could be dressed in a sack and still make a fortune masturbating on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Your Daughter" Chance="33">
                You probably shouldn't be watching your own daughter doing this,
                but ${name}'s so damn good it's impossible not to.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s shows are always sold out, and her fame is spreading across the city.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} stripped in a unique way tonight, dancing with a razor in each hand.
                With those razors, she peeled her clothes away from her lovely body,
                without nicking herself a single time.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                It's amazing how many tricks ${name} knows,
                to tease her audience but never quite push them over the point where they'd lose interest.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A simple smile towards the audience from ${name} makes every gambler howl and cheer.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} has a large devoted group of fans, who come in every night to watch her.
            </Text>
        </Message>
        <Message Name="work.great">
            She's unbelievable at this and is always getting praised by the customers for her work.


            <Text Condition="Nymphomaniac" Chance="33">
                ${name} loves her job.
                You can tell by the zeal she employs as she penetrates her mouth and pussy with dildoes on stage,
                moaning throughout.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Exhibitionist" Chance="33">
                ${name} feels so comfortable naked in front of strangers.
                She loves having all these strangers staring at her naked body
                and rewards the audience with a XXX show they will never forget.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="33">
                The skill of ${name}'s dancing coupled with her sexual air just pack the customers in.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                From start to finish, every move ${name} makes practically sweats sexuality.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} moved off the stage halfway through the act and walked amongst the audience, to their joy.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                As clothing slowly fell from her body and her hand descended towards her core,
                ${name} smiled seductively at the audience.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                All male members of ${name}'s audience had trouble standing after she fellated a dildo on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Amusingly, one of the female members of ${name}'s audience threw her panties on the stage,
                where ${name} used them as an impromptu prop.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.good">
            She's good at this job and gets praised by the customers often.

            <Text Condition="Long Legs" Chance="33">
                ${name}'s erotic dances are accentuated by her perfect legs.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="50">
                ${name} is by no measure bad at her job, but she gets way more customers than could be expected.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A man made an offer to buy ${name} today, which you turned down. She's popular with the patrons.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                You watched with amusement as members of her audience made a
                disproportionate number of trips to the bathroom after her performance.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                After letting ${name} choose the music that she danced to, her erotic dances have improved markedly.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} has a small, but devoted fanbase, who are willing to pay gate fees just to watch her dance.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                A lucky gambler almost fainted when ${name} gave him her freshly removed skirt as a present.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.ok">
            She made a few mistakes but overall she is okay at this.

            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="33">
                ${name}'s dances are mechanical, but her aurora of sexuality make clients break out in sweats.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Long Legs" Chance="33">
                Although ${name} is no great shake at this job, her legs lend her a significant popularity boost.
            </Text>
            <Group Chance="50">
                ${name} got a round of applause when she bowed, and an even bigger one when her
                <Text Condition="Abnormally Large Boobs|Titanic Tits|Massive Melons">
                    enormous breasts "accidentally" burst out from her top.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Big Boobs|Busty Boobs|Giant Juggs">
                    large breasts "accidentally" flopped out of her top.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Small Boobs|Petite Breasts">
                    shirt "accidentally" exposed her small and perky breasts.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Flat Chest">
                    shirt "accidentally" exposed the nipples on her perfectly flat chest.
                </Text>
                <Text Priority="-1">
                    breasts "accidentally" fell out of her top.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text>
                ${name} has some talent at this job, but she needs to develop it.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The cleaners always hate having to clean up after ${name}'s audience.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is not the best erotic dancer you've ever seen, but the gamblers enjoy the eyecandy.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s striptease draws a decent crowd each night.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.bad">
            She was nervous and made a few mistakes. She isn't that good at this.

            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="33">
                Even though a block of wood could dance better, ${name} still draws the eye.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Slut" Chance="33">
                A total slut,
                ${name} tried to liven up her show by getting one of the security team to fuck her on stage.
                He refused.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Long Legs" Chance="33">
                The perfectly sculpted flesh of her leg drew attention away from the stupid look on ${name}'s face.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} isn't qualified as a stripper,
                which might explain why she couldn't successfully detach her bra on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s hips twitched in a decidedly half-assed way.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                The only person who seemed to find ${name}'s striptease appetizing was a random drunk.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s distaste for the crowd was evident by her curled lip and perpetual scowl.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} is still incredibly sexy, despite her lack of anything resembling an active customer appeal.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="work.worst">
            She was nervous and constantly making mistakes. She really isn't very good at this job.

            <Text Condition="Long Legs" Chance="33">
                Customers just can't tear their eyes away from ${name}'s long, tasty legs,
                even as she tripped over her discarded top.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Strong Gag Reflex|Gag Reflex" Chance="33">
                ${name} was sucking off a dildo, when she made herself gag and threw up on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="skill:Magic<20" Chance="50">
                ${name} tried using magic light to enhance her show, but ended up setting her pubic hair on fire.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Sexy Air" Chance="33">
                Even though a block of wood could dance better, ${name} still draws the eye.
            </Text>
            <Text Condition="Alcoholic">
                ${name} was drunk when she stumbled out at the beginning of shift.
                She threw up and fell asleep on the floor almost as soon as she reached the stage.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Somehow, ${name} managed to be so unsexy that the audience barely seemed to notice her presence.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                Seeing the large crowd waiting outside, ${name}'s nerve broke, and she ran back out of the gambling hall.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name}'s hair got tangled up in her shirt when she tried to take it off,
                making her reel about the stage like a drunk.
            </Text>
            <Text>
                ${name} slipped on a fresh smear of ejaculate halfway through her dance, and fell on her ass.
            </Text>
        </Message>

        <Message Name="after-work">
            <Group Condition="Pessimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance<175" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    Her pessimism made her unadventurous. The customers were unimpressed and the tips were lower.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} performed well despite her mood.
                    The customers enjoy the darker, sultry nature of her sex shows.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Optimist" Chance="5">
                <Text Condition="Performance<175" Updates="Tips-=10">
                    ${name} smiled far too much to look seductive.
                </Text>
                <Text Condition="Performance>125" Updates="Tips+=10">
                    ${name} showed endless energy, agility and enthusiasm as she rucked around the stage.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Group Condition="Clumsy" Chance="15">
                Her clumsy nature caused her to lose one of her "toys" up a hole.
                <Text Updates="Tips+=10" Chance="50">
                    She put on a damn sexy show of getting it back out.
                </Text>
                <Text Updates="Tips-=10">
                    She panicked and ran off stage to go find a doctor.
                </Text>
            </Group>
            <Text Chance="20" Condition="stat:Beauty>85" Updates="Tips+=25">
                Stunned by her beauty a customer left her a great tip.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="10" Condition="Cat Girl" Updates="Tips+=15">
                ${name} is able to clean herself like a cat. Customers are amazed as this pussy-cat
                spreads her legs wide and licks her own cunt right there on stage.
            </Text>
            <Text Chance="10" Condition="Masochist" Updates="Tips+=15">
                <!-- TODO Health -->
                ${name} invites a few customers to punish her on stage. They happily agree to spank and whip her.
            </Text>
        </Message>
    </Messages>
</Job>